--==CMCT團隊榮譽出品==--
字幕調校:hanksking   影片壓制:暮雲春樹
招募Q號:76846146
片名:搏擊俱樂部
總是有人問我認不認識泰勒 德頓
People always ask me if I know Tyler Durden.
還有三分鐘
Three minutes.
精彩時刻就要到了 一切重新回到原來的起點
This is it. Ground zero.
你想說幾句話紀念這個偉大的時刻嗎?
Do you have a speech for the occasion?
嘴裡含著槍 只能支支唔唔的
With a gun barrel between your teeth, you speak only in vowels.
我還是沒想到要說什麼
I can't think of anything.
我差點忘了泰勒控制著破壞行動
For a second, I forget about Tyler's controlled demolition thing
不知道那把槍有多髒
and I wonder how clean that gun is.
越來越刺激了
It's getting exciting now.
俗話說 人們總會傷害他所愛的人
That old thing, how you always hurt the one you love.
其實人們也會愛上他所傷害的人
Well, it works both ways.
這出爆破戲 我們坐在最前排
We have front-row seats for this theater of mass destruction.
大破壞計畫準備炸毀12棟樓
The Demolitions Committee of Project Mayhem wrapped the foundations of 12 buildings with explosives.
2 分鐘後 炸彈就會被引爆
In two minutes, primary charges will blow base charges
好幾條街都會處於悶燒的狀態
and a few blocks will be reduced to smouldering rubble.
我知道這些 是因為泰勒他知道這些
I know this because Tyler knows this.
還有兩分鐘半 想想我們過去的成就吧
Two and a half. Think of everything we've accomplished.
突然間我終於明白了
Suddenly I realize that all of this,
槍 炸彈 革命...
the gun, the bombs, the revolution,
都跟瑪拉辛格這女人有關
has got something to do with a girl named Marla Singer.
鮑伯有大奶奶
Bob. Bob had bitch tits.
這是睾丸癌患者的安撫團體
This was a support group for men with testicular cancer.
這個把我抱了個滿懷的就是鮑伯
The big moosie slobbering all over me, that was Bob.
我們都還是男人
We're still men.
沒錯 我們是男人
Yes, we're men.
我們就是男人
Men is what we are.
鮑伯8個月前切除了睾丸 接著做荷爾蒙治療
Eight months ago Bob had his testicles removed. Then hormone therapy.
他的睾丸激素太高 刺激雌激素
He developed bitch tits because his testosterone was too high
所以他長了奶子
and his body upped the oestrogen.
－ 這裡很適合我...  - 他們又要切開我胸部減胸了
- That was where I fit... - They'll have to drain my pecs again.
頭被埋在這麼大的奶子中間
...between those huge sweating tits
不禁認為上帝的胸部也很壯觀
that hung enormous, the way you'd think of God's as big.
換你哭了
OK, you cry now.
先等等 讓我從頭說起
No, wait. Back up. Let me start earlier.
6個月來我都沒法閉眼
For six months, I couldn't sleep.
失眠症讓我感受不到真實
With insomnia, nothing's real.
一切都很虛幻
Everything's far away.
事情都成了相同的拷貝
Everything's a copy of a copy
探索外太空會找到一堆企業
When deep space exploration ramps up, it'll be the corporations that name everything.
IBM星球
The IBM Stellar Sphere.
微軟銀河系
The Microsoft Galaxy.
星巴克星球
The Planet Starbucks.
我要你到外地去處理些疑難雜症
I need you out of town this week to cover some red flags.
今天一定是星期二
It must have been Tuesday.
因為他系著藍色矢車菊領帶
He had on his cornflower blue tie.
我暫時放下手頭的工作?
You want me to deprioritize my reports...
先處理這些事件
until you advise of a status upgrade?
這是機票折價券 如果遇到臨時狀況再通知我
Prioritize these. Here's your flight coupons. Call me if there's any snags.
他很有精神
He was full of pep.
一定是喝了不少咖啡
Must have had his grande latte enema.
我也是個迷上傢俱裝潢的人
Like so many others, I had become a slave to the Ikea nesting instinct.
我要訂傢俱防塵腳套
Yes. I'd like to order the Erika Pekkari dust ruffles.
請等一下
Please hold.
要是看到陰陽形狀的咖啡桌
Anything clever, like a coffee table in the shape of a yin-yang,
我就一定要買到
I had to have it.
整組個人咖啡杯
The Klipsk personal office unit.
家用固定腳踏車
The Hovetrekke home exerbike.
綠色條紋的高級沙發
Or the Ohamshab sofa with the Strinne green stripe pattern.
還有裝著再生紙燈罩的電燈
Even the Ryslampa wire lamps of environmentally-friendly unbleached paper.
我翻著產品目錄思考著...
I'd flip through catalogues and wonder
哪種餐具能表現我的個人風格?
"What kind of dining set defines me as a person?"
連有瑕疵的盤子我都買了
I had it all. Even the glass dishes with tiny bubbles and imperfections,
因為它們是純手工製作的
proof that they were crafted by the honest, hard-working, indigenous peoples of...
- 請再稍等片刻  - 管他呢
- Please hold. - ...wherever.
反正我已經等很久了
I was hold.
以前我們看色情圖片尋找刺激
We used to read pornography.
現在是看產品目錄
Now it was the Horchow collection.
失眠症不會死人的
No. You can't die of insomnia.
嗜睡症呢?
What about narcolepsy?
突然睡著 在陌生的地方醒來
I nod off, I wake up in strange places. I have no idea how I got there.
你得放鬆心情
You need to lighten up.
給我些安眠藥吧?
Can you please just give me something?
紅紅藍藍的安眠藥
Red and blue Tuinals, lipstick-red Seconals...
不行 你需要健康自然的睡眠
No. You need healthy, natural sleep.
吃點拔地麻根 多做運動
Chew some valerian root and get more exercise.
別走嘛 我很痛苦啊
Hey, come on. I'm in pain.
星期二到教堂去見識見識真正的痛苦
You wanna see pain? Swing by First Methodist, Tuesday nights.
看看那些得了睾丸癌的人
See the guys with testicular cancer.
那才叫痛苦
That's pain.
我一直想要三個孩子
I always wanted three kids...
兩男一女
two boys and a girl.
敏蒂要兩女一男
Mindy wanted two girls and a boy.
我倆意見一直不合
We never could agree on anything.
她上禮拜生了第一個寶寶
Well, I... She...She had her first child last week.
是女孩
A girl.
是她新任丈夫的
With... With her... With her new husband.
操！
Fuck!
謝天謝地
Thank God, you know...
我真為她高興
I'm glad for her.
因為那是應該的
She deserves...
謝謝湯瑪斯與我們分享
Everyone, let's thank Thomas for sharing himself with us.
謝謝湯瑪斯...
Thank you, Thomas.
我看到各位的勇氣
I look around this room, and I see a lot of courage.
也帶給我力量
And that gives me strength.
我們互相給予彼此力量
We give each other strength.
一對一的時間到了
It's time for the one-on-ones.
以湯瑪斯的例子為準則 敞開心胸吧
So let's all of us follow Thomas's example and really open ourselves up.
請各自尋找搭檔
Could you find a partner?
我就是這樣認識大奶奶的
And this is how I met the big moosie.
他的眼睛早就熱淚盈眶
His eyes already shrink-wrapped in tears.
膝蓋摩擦著 小碎步走向我
Knees together. Those awkward little steps.
- 我是鮑伯  - 鮑伯
- My name is Bob. - Bob?
他曾是健美先生
Bob had been a champion bodybuilder.
你知道晚間的健胸節目嗎?
You know that chest expansion programme on late-night TV?
那是他提出的主意
That was his idea.
我曾經使用禁藥
I was a juicer.
就是類固醇
You know, using steroids?
戴伯諾
Diabonal and
威斯特駱
Wisterol.
那是拿來打在賽馬身上的
Oh, they use that on racehorses, for Christ sakes.
我破產了 離婚了
And now I'm bankrupt. I'm divorced.
我的兩個孩子
My two grown kids
他們甚至不肯回電話給我
won't even return my phone calls.
這麼坦白的陌生人 讓我想哭
Strangers with this kind of honesty make me go a big, rubbery one.
沒關係 柯納裡斯
Go ahead,... Cornelius.
好好的哭一場吧
You can cry.
接著奇跡發生了
And then... something happened.
我不再壓抑
I let go.
不顧一切
Lost in oblivion.
感到黑暗 沉默和完整
Dark and silent and complete.
我找到了自由 拋開所有希望就是自由
I found freedom. Losing all hope was freedom.
沒關係
It's OK.
初生的嬰兒都沒有我睡的沉
Babies don't sleep this well.
後來我就上癮了
I became addicted.
"酒精中毒 貪食症團體"
"如何對抗肺結核"
如果我不說話
If I didn't say anything
別人都會以為我快死了
people always assumed the worst.
"遠離病毒"
他們哭得越凶
They cried harder...
我就哭得越凶
then I cried harder.
"皮膚癌 腎臟癌 胃癌"
打開那扇綠門 你的心門
Now we're going to open the green door, the heart chakra...
我沒有絕症
I wasn't really dying.
也沒有癌症或是寄生菌
I wasn't host to cancer or parasites.
我只是一個小小的中心
I was the warm little center that the life of this world crowded around.
想像有一道治療你的白光
Imagine your pain as a white ball of healing light.
那道光在你身上遊移 治療
It moves over your body, healing you.
繼續冥想 別忘了呼吸
Now keep this going. Remember to breathe
走向房間的後門
and step forward through the back door of the room.
那道門通往哪裡?
Where does it lead?
到你的洞裡去
To your cave.
走進你的洞裡
Step forward into your cave.
很好
That's right.
走進洞的深處
You're going deeper into your cave.
你會在那裡找到你的精神動物
And you're going to find your power animal.
滑啊
Slide.
我每晚都會死一次
Every evening I died.
可是又重生一次
And every evening I was born again.
復活過來
Resurrected.
鮑伯以為我的睾丸也被切除了
Bob loved me because he thought my testicles were removed too.
我靠著他的奶子 準備哭泣
Being there, pressed against his tits, ready to cry.
這簡直是我的假期
This was my vacation.
但是她...
And she
卻把一切都給毀了
ruined everything.
這是癌症吧?
This is cancer, right?
瑪拉辛格根本沒有睾丸癌
This chick, Marla Singer, did not have testicular cancer.
她是騙子
She was a liar.
她根本沒有病
She had no diseases at all.
週二我還在血癌團體課見過她
I had seen her at Free And Clear, my blood parasites group, Thursdays.
還有我的鐮狀細胞貧血症團體
Then at Hope, my bimonthly sickle-cell circle.
還有"把握今天"
And again, at Seize The Day,
星期五晚上的肺結核團體
my tuberculosis, Friday night.
瑪拉
Marla,
這個到處都去的人
the big tourist.
她的謊言反射出我的謊言
Her lie reflected my lie.
突然間我沒有感覺了
And suddenly, I felt nothing.
我哭不出來了
I couldn't cry.
所以再一次的
So once again,
我睡不著了
I couldn't sleep.
下一節課 在冥想結束後
Next group, after guided meditation,
在敞開心房相互擁抱的時候
after we open our heart chakras, when it's time to hug,
我要抓著她的手大喊
I'm gonna grab that bitch, Marla Singer, and scream.
"瑪拉 你這個騙子 你給我滾"
Marla, you liar! You big tourist, I need this! Now, get out!
我4天沒睡了
I hadn't slept in four days.
得失眠症的人無法真正入睡
We'll just let that dry...When you have insomnia, you're never really asleep.
也沒有清醒的時刻
And you're never really awake.
今晚由克蘿伊替我們開場白
To begin tonight's communion, Chloe would like to say a few words.
對了 克蘿伊
Oh, yeah. Chloe.
她是那種讓人看上去...
Chloe looked the way Meryl Streep's skeleton would
非常有親和力的人
look if you made it walk around being extra nice to everybody.
嗨 我還活著
Well, I'm still here.
可是不知道會活多久
But I don't know for how long.
沒有人能給我正確答案
That's as much certainty as anyone can give me.
但我有個好消息
But I've got some good news.
我不害怕死亡了
I no longer have any fear of death.
可是我現在很孤獨
But... I am in a pretty lonely place.
沒有人願意跟我做愛
No-one will have sex with me.
我快死了 我想做最後一次愛
I'm so close to the end, and all I want is to get laid for the last time.
我家裡有A片
I have pornographic movies in my apartment,
- 還有潤滑劑和春藥...  - 謝謝你 克蘿伊
- and lubricants and amyl nitrite. - Thank you, Chloe.
我們謝謝克蘿伊
Everyone, let's thank Chloe.
謝謝 克蘿伊
Thank you, Chloe.
我們準備冥想吧
Now, let's ready ourselves for guided meditation.
你站在山洞的入口
You're standing at the entrance of your cave.
進入山洞往裡面走
You step inside your cave and you walk...
瑪拉猶如我的癌症
If I did have a tumor,
就像長在嘴邊的爛疽一般
I'd name it Marla.
瑪拉
Marla.
不去舔就不會惡化 但沒辦法不去舔
The scratch on the roof of your mouth that would heal if you could stop tonguing it.
再走深入一點
But you can't.
在你走的同時 感受身邊治療的力量
..deeper into your cave as you walk.
你感應到了治癒你的能量 去找你的精神動物
You feel a healing energy all around you. Now find your power animal.
滑啊
Slide.
開始分組吧
OK. Let's partner up.
選一個今晚對你很特別的人
Pick someone special to you tonight.
嘿
Hey.
- 我要跟你談談  - 好啊
- We need to talk. - Sure.
我知道你的底細
I'm onto you.
什麼?
What?
你是假的 你根本不會死
Yeah. You're a faker. You're not dying.
你說什麼?
Sorry?
某種觀點看來 我們都會死
In the Tibetan-philosophy, Sylvia-Plath sense of the word, I know we're all dying.
- 可是你跟克蘿伊的情況不同  - 怎樣?
- But you're not dying the way Chloe is. - So?
你什麼團體都參加
So you're a tourist.
我見過你 你參加過黑腫瘤課 肺結核課
I've seen you. I saw you at melanoma, I saw you at tuberculosis.
還有睾丸癌團體
I saw you at testicular cancer!
你演練過了對吧?
I saw you practising this.
演練什麼?
Practising what?
跟我對質的話啊
Telling me off.
結果與你預期一樣嗎? 陸波?
Is it going as well as you hoped...Rupert?
我要揭露你的事
I'll expose you.
去啊 我也會揭露你的事
Go ahead. I'll expose you.
好了 大家一起發洩吧
Come together. Let yourselves cry.
你為什麼要這樣子?
Oh, God. Why are you doing this?
這比看電影便宜 還有咖啡喝
It's cheaper than a movie and there's free coffee.
這是很重要的
Look, this is important.
那些是屬於我的團體 我參加這些團體1年了
These are my groups. I've been coming for over a year.
- 你又是為什麼?  - 不清楚
- Why do you do it? - I don't know.
快死的人 說話特別有份量
When people think you're dying, they listen to you instead of...
別人不敢打斷
Instead of waiting for their turn to speak.
沒錯
Yeah. Yeah.
完全分享你的事
Share yourself... completely.
你不會想繼續下去了 你會上癮的
Look, you don't want to get into this. It becomes an addiction.
真的?
Really?
我說真的
I'm not kidding.
我需要這些課程好好哭泣
I can't cry if another faker is present, and I need this.
請你另覓他處
You gotta find somewhere else to go.
那是你的問題 可不關我的事
Candystripe a cancer ward. It's not my problem.
等一下 別走
No, wait a second. Hold on.
我們平分好了
We'll split up the week, OK?
淋巴瘤和肺結核給你
You take lymphoma and tuberculosis.
肺結核給你 我太愛抽煙了
You take tuberculosis. My smoking doesn't go over at all.
好 睾丸癌沒有爭議吧?
OK. Good. Fine. Testicular cancer should be no contest.
我比你有資格去
Technically, I have more right to be there.
因為你還有睾丸
You still have your balls.
你在開玩笑吧?
You're kidding.
你看像嗎?
I dunno. Am I?
不
No. No.
那你要什麼?
What do you want?
寄生菌
I'll take the parasites.
你不能都要 血液寄生菌給你好了
You can't have both. Take the blood parasites.
- 我要腦寄生菌  - 我也要腦寄生菌
- I want brain parasites. - I'll take the blood but I want brain dementia.
- 我要  - 腦部分很多區 你不能通通去
- I want that. - You can't have the whole brain.
你分到四個 我只分到兩個
So far, you have four. I only have two.
好吧 寄生菌都給你
OK. Take both the parasites. They're yours.
我們兩都各分到三個了
Now we both have three...
你的衣服掉了
Hey! You left half your clothes.
你賣髒衣服?
What, are you selling those?
沒錯 我是賣衣服的
Yes! I'm selling some clothes!
我們各三天 那一共六天
So! We each have three. That's six.
第七天呢? 我要腸癌
What about the seventh day? I want bowel cancer.
她也下過功夫
The girl had done her homework.
我要腸癌
No. No. I want bowel cancer.
那也是你的最愛? 那麼我們分吧?
That's your favorite too? Tried to slip it by me, eh?
好 我們分配一下 你每個月的單數周去
Look, we'll split it. Take the first and third Sunday.
好
Deal.
看來要道別了
Looks like this is goodbye.
沒什麼大不了的
Let's not make a big thing out of it.
這當然沒什麼大不了
How's this for not making a big thing?
瑪拉
Hey, Marla!
Marla!
我們交換電話號碼吧
Maybe we should exchange numbers.
要嗎?
Should we?
- 或許有時會想換時間啊  - 好
- We might wanna switch nights. - OK.
我就是這樣認識瑪拉辛格的
This is how I met Marla Singer.
瑪拉的哲學是 她隨時都會死
Marla's philosophy of life was that she might die at any moment.
悲慘的是 她一直都沒死
The tragedy, she said, was that she didn't.
你沒寫名字 你是誰?
It doesn't have your name! Who are you?
柯裡納斯? 陸波?
Cornelius? Rupert?
崔維斯? 到底是哪個蠢名字?
Travis? Any of the stupid names you give each night?
我在西雅圖機場上醒來 或三藩市機場 或洛城機場
You wake up at SeaTac. SFO. LAX.
或歐哈機場
You wake up at O'Hare.
或達拉斯機場
Dallas Fort Worth.
或巴華機場
BWI.
太平洋 山區 或中央時區
Pacific. Mountain. Central.
有時多一小時 有時少一小時
Lose an hour. Gain an hour.
兩小時前就要辦登機手續 先生
The check-in for that flight isn't for another two hours, sir.
你的生命一分一分的消逝
This is your life, and it's ending one minute at a time.
在哈柏國際機場醒來
You wake up at Air Harbor International.
若在不同時間於不同地點醒來
If you wake up at a different time, in a different place,
你會變成不同的人嗎?
could you wake up as a different person?
我不管到哪 都有瑣事
Everywhere I travel, tiny life.
一包糖 一包奶精
Single-serving sugar and cream.
一包奶油
Single pat of butter.
方型的微波爐餐
The microwave cordon bleu hobby kit.
旅行用洗髮精組
Shampoo-conditioner combos.
簡單的牙刷牙膏 小肥皂
Sample-package mouthwash. Tiny bars of soap.
我在每架飛機上遇到的人
The people I meet on each flight,
也都是一面之緣的朋友
they're single-serving friends.
在起飛和降落前 我們相互之間分享一點時間
Between takeoff and landing, we have our time together. That's all we get.
歡迎
Welcome!
總之時間一到 大家都翹辮子
On a long enough time line, the survival rate for everyone drops to zero.
我是一名汽車召回協調員 我的工作就是使用一些公式
I was a recall coordinator. My job was to apply the formula.
那個嬰兒就是從擋風玻璃這地方被甩出來的 這個三分
The infant went through the windshield.
這是我們公司的新車款 時速60英里
A new car built by my company leaves somewhere traveling at 60mph.
後輪差速排檔鎖死了
The rear differential locks up.
有個孩子的牙套留在後座的煙灰缸上
The teenager's braces are stuck to the ashtray.
這個畫面可以做戒煙廣告
Might make a good anti-smoking ad.
車子撞擊時 人都還在車內
The car crashes and burns with everyone trapped inside.
需要回收這款車型嗎?
Now, should we initiate a recall?
這爸爸一定很胖
The father must have been huge.
你看座位上被燒的肥油痕跡
See where the fat burned to the seat? The polyester shirt?
很有現代藝術感
Very modern art.
將這輛車的序號 A
Take the number of vehicles in the field, A.
乘以故障機率 B
Multiply it by the probable rate of failure, B.
再乘以官司需要的費用 C
Multiply the result by the average out-of-court settlement, C.
A乘以B乘以C等於X
A x B x C equals X.
若X小於善後處理費用的話
If X is less than the cost of a recall,
我們就不做車型的回收
we don't do one.
這種意外很多嗎?
Are there a lot of these kinds of accidents?
多到你無法相信
You wouldn't believe.
你是哪家汽車公司的?
Which car company do you work for?
很大的那家
A major one.
只要飛機搖晃的厲害時
Every time the plane banked too sharply on takeoff or landing,
我都祈禱能墜機或是爆炸 什麼都行
I prayed for a crash or a midair collision. Anything.
出差保險理賠是一般的三倍
Life insurance pays off triple if you die on a business trip.
"如果您的座位是在緊急出口的旁邊"
"If you are seated in an emergency exit row
"而且您覺得自己無法承擔 或不願承擔安全指引卡所列明的義務"
and would be unable or unwilling to perform the duties
"請要求機組人員為您安排另一個座位"
listed on the safety card, please ask a flight attendant to reseat you."
你的責任很重呢?
It's a lot of responsibility.
你想要換位子嗎?
Wanna switch seats?
我沒辦法勝任那種工作
No. I'm not sure I'm the man for that particularjob.
3萬英尺高的緊急出口
An exit-door procedure at 30,000ft.
還有什麼安全可言
The illusion of safety.
就是說啊
Yeah. I guess so.
你知道機上為什麼有氧氣罩?
You know why they put oxygen masks on planes?
讓我們呼吸啊
So you can breathe.
是因為氧氣讓人興奮
Oxygen gets you high.
緊急狀況時 人會大口呼吸
In a catastrophic emergency, you take giant panic breaths.
吸了氧氣會有安定感
Suddenly you become euphoric, docile.
就會面對現實
You accept your fate.
上面都有寫
It's all right here.
緊急水上降落 時速6百英里
Emergency water landing, 600mph.
乘客每個都臉色慘白
Blank faces. Calm as Hindu cows.
你剛才說的...
That's...
那些理論很有趣
That's an interesting theory.
你是幹什麼的?
What do you do?
什麼意思?
What do you mean?
你是幹什麼工作的?
What do you do for a living?
幹嘛?
Why?
你會假裝你有興趣嗎?
So you can pretend you're interested?
你的笑聲裡帶著絕望
You have a kind of sick desperation in your laugh.
我們的公事包一模一樣
We have the exact same briefcase.
肥皂
Soap.
- 什麼?  - 我製造 銷售肥皂
- Sorry? - I make and I sell soap.
這些可是文明的產物
The yardstick of civilization.
我就是這樣認識了...
And this is how I met...
泰勒德頓
Tyler Durden.
等量的汽油和凍柳橙汁混合後
Did you know if you mix gasoline and frozen orange juice,
可以做成汽油彈喔 知道嗎?
you can make napalm?
不知道 這是真的嗎?
No, I did not. Is that true?
真的
That's right.
用家裡的小東西就能做炸彈
One can make all kinds of explosives with simple household items.
真的?
Really?
只要你想做
If one was so inclined.
你是我的一次性朋友裡頭最有趣的一個
Tyler, you are by far the most interesting single-serving friend I have ever met.
飛機上所有東西都是一次性的
Everything on a plane is single-serving...
我聽懂了 真聰明
Oh, I get it. Very clever.
謝謝
Thank you.
那樣對你有什麼好處?
How's it working out for you?
什麼?
What?
聰明啊
Being clever?
這很好啊
Great.
那就繼續保持吧
Keep it up, then. Right up.
一個關於禮儀的問題 當我出去時
A question of etiquette. As I pass,
我該面向著你 還是屁股向著你才有禮貌
do I give you the ass or the crotch?
我會跟泰勒住是有原因的
How I came to live with Tyler is...
因為航空公司討厭震動的行李
Airlines have this policy about vibrating luggage.
有滴答聲嗎?
Was it ticking?
丟手說現代炸彈是無聲的
Throwers know modern bombs don't tick.
丟手?
Sorry, throwers?
處理行李的人
Baggage handlers.
只要行李會震動 就得報警
But when a suitcase vibrates, the throwers have got to call the police.
我的行李會震動?
My suitcase was vibrating?
這情況十之八九是電動刮胡刀
Nine times out of ten it's an electric razor.
可是有時候是...
But... every once in a while
人造男性生殖震動器
it's a dildo.
那東西沒有列入我們的禁品
It's company policy never to imply ownership in the event of a dildo.
法條只說"人造男性生殖器" 而非"你的人造男性生殖器"
We have to use the indefinite article, a dildo, never your dildo.
我沒有...
I don't own...
我所有的東西都在裡面
I had everything in that suitcase.
我的凱文克萊襯衫
My CK shirts.
我的DKNY鞋子
My DKNYshoes.
我的AX領帶
My AX ties.
算了
Never mind.
嘿 那是我的車!
Hey! That's my car!
我的公寓是在15樓的小窩
Home was a condo on the 15th floor of a filing cabinet for widows and professionals.
四面都是水泥牆
The walls were solid concrete.
重要的是水泥牆
A foot of concrete is important
可以抵擋鄰居的噪音
when your next-door neighbor has to watch game shows at full volume
也能防止火山爆發時弄壞傢俱
Or when a blast of debris that used to be your personal effects
將傢俱甩出 燒得精光
blows out of your windows and sails flaming into the night.
這種事有可能發生的
I suppose these things happen.
上面什麼都沒有了
There's... nothing up there.
你不能進去 這是警方的命令
You can't go into the unit. Police orders.
你有人可以聯絡嗎?
Do you have somebody you can call?
真丟臉
How embarrassing.
房裡只有調味料 沒有東西吃
A houseful of condiments and no food.
"瑪拉辛格"
警方說可能是爐火火苗熄了
The police later told me the pilot light might have gone out
所以瓦斯外泄
letting out just a little bit of gas.
瓦斯慢慢充滿房裡
That gas could have filled the condo.
好幾天來慢慢累積
1700 square feet with high ceilings for days and days.
後來碰到冰箱壓縮機啟動...
Then the refrigerator's compressor could have clicked on.
喂?
Yeah?
我聽到你的呼吸...
I can hear you breathing...
我也不知道為什麼打電話找他
If you ask me now, I couldn't tell you why I called him.
- 喂?  - 你是哪位?
- Hello? - Who's this?
- 泰勒嗎?  - 你是誰?
- Tyler? - Who is this?
我們在飛機上見過
We met... We met on the airplane.
公事包一模一樣的
We had the same suitcase?
那個聰明人?
The clever guy?
對了
Oh, yeah. Right.
我剛才也打過
I called a second ago.
沒有人接電話 我是用的公用電話
There was no answer. I'm at a payphone.
我從不接電話 只回拔電話
Yeah, I never pick up my phone.
怎麼了?
So what's up?
說了你也不會相信
Well. You're not gonna believe this.
你知道嗎 這還算好的
You know, it could be worse.
萬一被女人割老二 再被她丟到別人車上才慘
A woman could cut off your penis while you sleep and toss it out of a car.
那種事也可能發生
There's always that. I don't know.
只是每次買傢俱時都會想
When you buy furniture, you tell yourself, that's it.
"這是我最後一次買沙發"
That's the last sofa I'll need.
"我要好好保護這套沙發"
Whatever happens, that sofa problem is handled.
我什麼都有 還有高級音響
I had it all. I had a stereo that was very decent.
漂亮的衣櫃
A wardrobe that was getting very respectable.
不用多久我就什麼都有了
I was close to being complete.
可是現在卻一無所有
Shit, man. Now it's all gone.
一無所有
All gone.
你聽過鴨絨墊子嗎?
Do you know what a duvet is?
- 棉被?  - 是毯子
- A comforter. - It's a blanket.
我們一定要知道鴨絨墊子嗎?
Just a blanket. Why do guys like you and I know what a duvet is?
我們一定要字字斟酌嗎?
Is this essential to our survival in the hunter-gatherer sense?
不用
No.
那你和我算什麼?
What are we, then?
消費者啊
I dunno. Consumers.
對 我們就是消費者
Right. We're consumers.
我們滿腦子想的都是物質
We are by-products of a lifestyle obsession.
我不關心兇殺案和貧窮問題
Murder, crime, poverty. These things don't concern me.
我只關心名人雜誌
What concerns me are celebrity magazines,
5百個頻道的電視
television with 500 channels,
我內褲上印著誰的名字
some guy's name on my underwear.
生髮劑 威爾鋼 減肥藥
Rogaine. Viagra. Olestra.
還有萬能的瑪莎
Martha Stewart.
去她的瑪莎
Fuck Martha Stewart.
瑪莎所造就的世界慢慢沉淪
She's polishing the brass on the Titanic. It's all going down.
去你的沙發和綠條紋沙發布
So fuck off with your sofa units and Strinne green stripe patterns.
不要讓自己什麼都有
I say never be complete.
不要做完美的人
I say stop being perfect.
我們要進化 水來土掩
I say let's evolve. Let the chips fall where they may.
那只是我的意見 也許我錯了
But that's me, and I could be wrong.
也許你很重視那些東西
Maybe it's a terrible tragedy.
只是一堆身外物 無所謂
It's just stuff. Not a tragedy...
你的確損失不少現代傢俱
You did lose a lot of versatile solutions for modern living.
沒錯 你說得對 哦不 我不抽煙
Fuck, you're right. I don't smoke.
我的保險會賠償的
My insurance is probably gonna cover it, so...
怎麼了?
What?
你已經被物質奴役了
The things you own end up owning you.
隨便你吧
Do what you like, man.
很晚了
Oh, it's late.
- 謝謝你請我喝酒  - 不客氣
- Hey, thanks for the beer. - Yeah, man.
我要找家飯店才行
I should find a hotel.
什麼?
What?
飯店?
A hotel?
是啊
Yeah.
開口問嘛
Just ask, man.
你說什麼?
What are you talking about?
噢 天 都喝三杯酒了 還不敢問
Oh, God. Three pitchers of beer and you still can't ask.
什麼?
What?
你找我是因為你沒地方住
You called me because you needed a place to stay.
我不是...
Oh, hey. No, no, no.
就是 開口說就是了
Yes, you did. So just ask.
別裝了 直接說吧
Cut the foreplay and just ask, man.
會給你帶來麻煩嗎?
Would... Would that be a problem?
你開口問會有什麼麻煩嗎?
Is it a problem for you to ask?
我可以到你家借住嗎?
Can I stay at your place?
可以
Yeah.
謝了
Thanks.
我要你幫我一個忙
I want you to do me a favor.
什麼忙?
Yeah, sure.
用力打我
I want you to hit me as hard as you can.
什麼?
What?
我要你用盡全力打我
I want you to hit me as hard as you can.
我先介紹泰勒德頓
Let me tell you a little bit about Tyler Durden.
他是個夜貓子
Tyler was a night person.
我們睡覺的時候他卻在工作
While the rest of us slept, he worked.
他兼職做放映師
He had one part-time job as a projectionist.
電影分好幾卷 並非一卷到底
A movie doesn't come all on one big reel. It comes on a few.
需要有人準確的
Someone has to switch the projectors at the exact moment
接上兩卷膠捲
that one reel ends and the next one begins.
你會在右上方看到小點點
You can see little dots come into the upper right corner of the screen.
我們的行話叫做香煙烙點
In the industry, we call them cigarette burns.
那就是換下一卷的記號
That's the cue for a changeover.
他在電影進行中換放映機
He flips the projectors,
觀眾毫不知情
movie keeps going and the audience has no idea.
怎麼會有人做這種爛工作?
Why would anyone want this shit job?
因為這樣他就能做怪
Because it affords him interesting opportunities.
把色情電影片段放入普級片中
Like splicing a frame of pornography into family films.
所以在看名人配音的卡通片時
So when the snooty cat and the courageous dog with the celebrity voices first meet,
就會發現泰勒的傑作
that's when you'll catch a flash of Tyler's contribution to the film.
觀眾根本沒察覺到自己看到了
Nobody knows that they saw it but they did.
好大的屌
Nice, big cock.
泰勒的動作快極了
Even a hummingbird couldn't catch Tyler at work.
他有時也在大飯店兼作侍者
Tyler also works sometimes as a banquet waiter at the luxurious Pressman hotel.
他是食品服務業的恐怖份子
He was the guerrilla terrorist of the food service industry.
別看我 我會尿不出來
Do not watch. I cannot go when you watch.
他有時會在甜點上放屁
Apart from seasoning the lobster bisque,
在萵苣火鍋裡擤鼻涕
he farted on meringues,
至於蘑菇湯上面的奶油...
and as for the cream of mushroom soup...
告訴他們啊
Go ahead, tell 'em.
你們猜到了吧
You get the idea.
你要我打你?
You just want me to hit you?
幫我一下嘛
Come on. Do me this one favor.
為什麼?
Why?
不知道 我沒打過架 你呢?
I don't know. Never been in a fight. You?
沒有 沒打過架很好啊
No. But that's a good thing.
沒幹過架 怎會瞭解自己?
You can't know yourself if you haven't!
我希望死的時候身上滿是傷痕
I don't wanna die without any scars.
- 來吧 在我還有勇氣的時候打我  - 噢 你這神經病
- Come on. Hit me, before I lose my nerve. - Oh, God. This is crazy.
發神經啊 快打我
So go crazy! Let it rip.
- 我覺得不好吧  - 管他呢
- I don't know about this. - I don't either.
又沒有人看見 你在乎什麼?
Who gives a shit? No-one's watching. What do you care?
你這瘋子 真的要我打你?
This is crazy. You want me to hit you?!
沒錯
That's right.
打哪裡? 打臉嗎?
Where? Like, in the face?
隨便你
Surprise me.
這主意真他媽蠢....
This is so fucking stupid.
去你的
Motherfucker!
你居然打我耳朵
He hit me in the ear!
- 對不起  - 喔哇 該死!
- Well, Jesus, I'm sorry. - Ow, Christ!
- 為什麼打我耳朵?  - 是我的錯
- Why the ear, man? - I fucked it up.
不 這樣很棒
No, that was perfect.
你沒事吧?
No, it's all right.
很痛啊
It really hurts.
沒錯
Right.
再打我一次
Hit me again.
換你打我了
No, you hit me.
打我啊
Come on!
我們應該再打一場
We should do this again sometime.
- 你的車呢?  - 什麼車?
- Where's your car? - What car?
不知道泰勒怎麼找到那地方
I don't know how Tyler found that house
他說他住在那裡一年了
but he said he'd been there for a year.
看起來好像快拆除的房子
It looked like it was waiting to be torn down.
窗戶都被封死了
Most of the windows were boarded up.
門也無法上鎖
There was no lock on the front door from when the police, or whoever, kicked it in.
樓梯隨時都會垮
The stairs were ready to collapse.
這裡是他的 還是偷住的?
I didn't know if he owned it or was squatting.
我覺得都有可能
Neither would have surprised me.
那是你的 那是我的
Yep. That's you. That's me.
那是廁所 可以吧?
That's the toilet. Good?
很好 謝謝
Yeah, thanks.
什麼爛地方
What a shithole.
什麼都不能用
Nothing worked.
開這盞燈 另一盞燈就會滅
Turning on one light meant another light in the house went out.
方圓百里只有倉庫和造紙廠
There were no neighbors. Just warehouses and a paper mill.
有蒸氣的惡臭
That fart smell of steam.
還有木頭的腐朽味道
The hamster-cage smell of wood chips.
等一下
What have we here?
你們好
Hey, guys.
碰到下雨 我們還得切掉電源
Every time it rained, we had to kill the power.
都月底了 我也不想看電視
By the end of the first month, I didn't miss TV.
更不在乎熱騰騰的冰箱
I didn't even mind the warm, stale refrigerator.
我下一個好嗎?
Can I be next?
好啊
All right, man.
鬆開領帶
Lose the tie.
晚上我和泰勒住在偏僻的房裡
At night,Tyler and I were alone for half a mile in every direction.
屋頂不斷漏下雨滴
Rain trickled down through the plaster and the light fixtures.
只要是木制的傢俱通通膨脹
Everything wooden swelled and shrank.
生蛌滌v子都跑了出來
Everywhere were rusted nails to snag your elbow on.
之前的住家一定都不出門
The previous occupant had been a shut-in.
你在讀什麼?
Hey, man. What are you reading?
看看這個 以某個器官做第一人稱的文章
Listen to this. It's an article written by an organ in the first person.
"我是傑克的脊髓"
"I am Jack's medulla oblongata. Without me,
"沒有了我 他就沒有心跳"
Jack could not regulate his heart rate or breathing."
這裡還有很多 "我是吉兒的乳頭"
There's a whole series of these. "I Am Jill's Nipples."
- "我是傑克的結腸"  - 呵呵 "我得了癌症 會害死傑克"
- "I Am Jack's Colon." - "I Get Cancer. I Kill Jack."
每次打架後 我的聽力就減弱
After fighting, everything else in life got the volume turned down.
什麼?
What?
什麼事情都迎刃而解
You could deal with anything.
報告寫完了嗎?
Have you finished those reports?
要是可以選擇 你最想跟誰打架?
If you could choose, who would you fight?
我老闆吧
I'd fight my boss, probably.
真的?
Really?
你呢? 你會和誰打架?
Yeah, why? Who would you fight?
我爸
I'd fight my dad.
我不認識我爸
I don't know my dad.
我認識他啦
I mean, I know him, but...
可是我六歲時 他就離開了
He left when I was like, six years old.
娶了另一個女人 生其他孩子
Married this other woman and had some other kids.
他每六年就換地方 重新成家
He did this every six years. He changes city and starts a new family.
他是在開分公司嗎?
Fucker's setting up franchises!
我爸沒讀大學
My dad never went to college.
- 所以我必須讀  - 這經歷聽起來很熟悉
- So it was real important that I go. - That sounds familiar.
我畢業後打電話給他
So I graduate. Call him up long-distance and say,
"爸 我現在要做什麼?"
"Dad, now what?"
他說"找工作啊"
He says, "Get ajob."
我也是
Same here.
我現在長大了 打電話給他
Now I'm 25. Make my yearly call again.
我問"爸 我現在要幹嘛?"
"Dad, now what?"
他說"不知道 結婚吧"
He says, "I dunno. Get married."
你不可能結婚的
You can't get married.
我是個30歲的小孩子
I'm a 30-year-old boy.
我們都是被女人養大的
We're a generation of men raised by women.
再找一個女人就可以了嗎?
I'm wondering if another woman is really the answer we need.
大多數時候 我倆互相照顧
Most of the week, we were Ozzie and Harriet.
可是每到週末夜晚 我們都要找事做
But every Saturday night, we were finding something out.
證明自己不是孤獨的
We were finding out more and more that we were not alone.
我以前要是帶著憤怒回家
It used to be that when I came home angry or depressed,
我會打掃公寓 替傢俱打蠟
I'd just clean my condo. Polish my Scandinavian furniture.
我早該另覓公寓
I should have been looking for a new condo
找保險公司辦理賠的
or haggling with my insurance company.
我應該要替我的失去感到難過
I should have been upset about my nice flaming little shit.
可是我沒有
But I wasn't.
各公司的網路著重在於效率
The premise of cybernetting an office is make things more efficient
在週一的早上 我只是期待下星期的來臨
Monday mornings, I just thought about next week.
用藍色做圖示好嗎?
Can I get the icon in cornflower blue?
好啊
Absolutely.
最重要的是效率
Efficiency is priority No.1, people.
因為浪費就是盜竊行為
Because waste is a thief.
我給朋友看過了 你喜歡吧?
I showed this to my man here. You liked it, didn't you?
只要喝一品脫的血就會生病
You can swallow a pint of blood before you get sick.
每個人臉上都有這種表情
It was right in everyone's face.
泰勒和我只是表現出來
Tyler and I just made it visible.
大家都這麼想
It was on the tip of everyone's tongue.
泰勒和我則直言不諱
Tyler and I just gave it a name.
各位 你們必須回家了
Come on, you've gotta go home!
關掉音樂 把後門鎖上
Turn off the jukebox. Lock the back.
泰勒每週都重述我倆訂的規則
Every week, Tyler gave the rules that he and I decided.
各位
Gentlemen!
歡迎來到搏擊俱樂部
Welcome to Fight Club.
搏擊俱樂部第一條規則
The first rule of Fight Club is
就是不能提及搏擊俱樂部
you do not talk about Fight Club.
搏擊俱樂部第二條規則
The second rule of Fight Club is
還是不能提及搏擊俱樂部
you do not talk about Fight Club!
第三條規則
Third rule of Fight Club.
只要有人喊停 四肢受傷 快累死了
Someone yells stop, goes limp, taps out,
打鬥就得停
the fight is over.
第四條規則 一次只能兩個人打
Fourth rule. Only two guys to a fight.
第五條...
Fifth rule.
一次一場
One fight at a time, fellas.
第六條 脫掉襯衫和鞋子打
Sixth rule. No shirts. No shoes.
第七條
Seventh rule.
打鬥沒有時限
Fights will go on as long as they have to.
第八條 也是最後一條
And the eighth and final rule.
如果你是初次參加
If this is your first night at Fight Club
就一定得打
you have to fight.
辦公室的小弟李奇
This kid from work, Ricky,
上班時什麼事都記不住
couldn't remember whether you ordered pens with blue ink or black.
但他打架的招式可是一流的
But Ricky was a god for ten minutes when he trounced the maitre d' of a local food court.
在?喊聲中 只聽得見打擊聲
Sometimes, all you could hear were the flat, hard, packing sounds over the yelling.
或是滿嘴是血的咳嗽聲
Or the wet choke when someone gasped and sprayed...
停
Stop!
在那裡 你才真正的活了起來
You weren't alive anywhere like you were there.
搏擊俱樂部只在聚會時存在
But Fight Club only exists in the hours between when Fight Club starts and ends.
就算是我認為打得很棒的人
Even if I could tell someone they had a good fight,
聚會結束後 也會馬上改變
I wouldn't be talking to the same man.
在俱樂部的你不是其他地方的你
Who you were in Fight Club is not who you were outside of it.
剛來俱樂部的人
A guy came to Fight Club for the first time.
屁股都是光滑圓潤
His ass was a wad of cookie dough.
幾周後 就像雕刻過的木頭
After a few weeks, he was carved out of wood.
假如可以選擇 你最想跟哪個名人打?
If you could fight any celebrity, who would you fight?
- 活的還是死的?  - 都可以 誰最難打?
- Alive or dead? - Doesn't matter. Who'd be tough?
海明威
Hemingway.
你呢?
You?
沙特納
Shatner.
我要跟威廉沙特納打
I'd fight William Shatner.
我們開始有不同觀點
We all started seeing things differently.
不管到哪 我們都會評論
Everywhere we went, we were sizing things up.
我覺得上健身房的人真可悲
I felt sorry for guys packed into gyms,
以凱文克萊的標準為目標
trying to look like how Calvin Klein or Tommy Hilfiger said they should.
那是男人應該有的樣子嗎?
Is that what a man looks like?
自我成長要靠手淫
Oh, self-improvement is masturbation.
自我毀滅...
Now, self-destruction...
對不起
Excuse me.
搏擊俱樂部不在乎輸贏
Fight Club wasn't about winning or losing.
也不需要言語
It wasn't about words.
真正的?喊聲含在嘴裡
The hysterical shouting was in tongues
跟聖靈降臨教派類似
like at a Pentecostal Church.
- 怎麼樣?  - 停...
- Is that it? - Stop!
打架結束後 不需要處理問題
When the fight was over, nothing was solved.
因為一切都沒關係
But nothing mattered.
真棒
Cool.
打過之後 猶如被救贖一般
Afterwards, we all felt saved.
嘿 夥計 下禮拜怎樣?
Hey, man. How about next week?
下個月呢?
How about next month?!
說話小心點 艾文到中間來
Irvine, you're in the middle.
新來的也過來
New guy, you too.
有時候泰勒會替我說話
Sometimes, Tyler spoke for me.
他從樓梯上摔了下來
He fell down some stairs.
我從樓梯上摔了下來
I fell down some stairs.
因為俱樂部 我剪髮剪指甲
Fight Club became the reason to cut your hair short or trim your fingernails.
歷史上的人物呢?
OK. Any historical figure.
我會跟甘地打
I'd fight Gandhi.
好答案
Good answer.
你呢?
How about you?
林肯
Lincoln.
林肯?
Lincoln?
他很高大 會打到快死才肯停
Big guy, big reach. Skinny guys fight till they're burger.
操
Fuck!
年紀大了 不中用了
Hey, even the Mona Lisa's falling apart.
喂?
Hello?
你這兩個月到哪去了?
Where have you been the last eight weeks?
瑪拉?
Marla?
你怎麼找到我的?
How did you find me?
你在答錄機上留的
You left a forwarding number.
我都沒在團體課上看見你
I haven't seen you at any support groups.
因為我們分開上了啊
We split 'em up. That was the idea. Remember?
可是你也沒去上你的課啊
Yeah, but you haven't been going to yours.
你怎麼知道?
How do you know?
我作弊了
I cheated.
我找到一個新的
I found a new one.
真的?
Really?
只有男人可以參加
It's for men only.
跟睾丸癌一樣嗎?
Like the testicle thing?
我現在不能跟你談
Look, this is a bad time.
我參加了花錢狂治療團體
I've been going to Debtors Anonymous.
- 那裡到處都是毫無希望的人...  - 我剛好要出門
- They're really fucked-up people... - I'm on my way out.
我也是 我吃了好多安眠藥
Me too. I've got a stomach full of Xanax.
把瓶子裡的通通吃光了
I took what was left of a bottle.
可能吃太多了吧
It might have been too much.
我想像著瑪拉在家裡蹣跚的樣子
Picture Marla Singer throw herself around her crummy apartment.
我並不想自殺 只是想求助 (她可能要搞好幾個小時)
This isn't a for-real suicide thing. This is probably a cry-for-help thing.
你今晚會在家囉?
So you're staying in tonight, then?
要不要聽我描述死亡?
Do you wanna wait and hear me describe death?
等著看我有多少精神講電話
Do you wanna listen and see if my spirit can use a phone?
聽過死前的喘息嗎?
Have you ever heard a death rattle before?
泰勒的門關著
Tyler's door was closed.
這兩個月來 他的門從沒關過
I'd been here for two months and his door was never closed.
我做了一個很誇張的夢
You won't believe this dream I had last night.
我也不敢相信昨晚的事
I can hardly believe anything about last night.
你怎麼會在這裡?
What are you doing here?
什麼?
What?
這是我家 你怎麼會在我家?
This is my house. What are you doing here?
去你的
Fuck you!
你朋友真的被搞死了
Oh, you've got some fucked-up friends!
可是她很有彈性
Limber, though.
愚蠢的性玩具
Silly cooze.
昨天晚上我回來 看到電話沒掛
I come in last night. Phone's off the hook.
想聽聽看是誰?
Guess who's on the other end?
不用他說 我就知道經過了
I knew the story before he told me.
聽過死前的喘息嗎?
Have you ever heard a death rattle before?
你覺得這名字響亮嗎?
Do you think it'll live up to its name?
說不定我只會發出乾咳聲
Or will it just be a death hairball?
或者是將靈魂帶到...
Prepare to evacuate soul.
10...
Ten,
9...
nine...
8...
eight...
泰勒和其他的人 為什麼不希望瑪拉死?
How could Tyler, of all people, think it was a bad thing that Marla Singer was about to die?
5...
Five,
4...
four...
3...等一下
three...Hang on.
你跑來得真快
You got here fast.
我有打電話給你嗎?
Did I call you?
床罩太滑了
The mattress is all sealed in slippery plastic.
別擔心 那東西不會傷害你
Oh, don't worry. It's not a threat to you.
糟糕 有人報警了
Oh, fuck! Somebody called the cops.
513房在哪裡?
Hey, where's 513?
最後一間
End of the hall.
裡面那個女孩本來很好的
The girl who lives there used to be a charming, lovely girl.
可是她失去了自信
She has lost faith in herself.
辛格小姐 我們是來幫你的
Miss Singer, let us help you!
她是個怪物
She's a monster!
你不可以死
You have every reason to live.
她是個骯髒的人渣
She's infectious human waste!
祝你們救得到她
Good luck trying to save her!
要是我睡著就死定了
If I fall asleep, I'm done for.
所以你必須保持我清醒
You're gonna have to keep me up
一整晚喔
all night.
太不可思議了
Un-fucking-believable.
他很輕易地解決了瑪拉的問題
He was obviously able to handle it.
你也知道的 因為你跟她幹過
You know what I mean, you fucked her.
我沒有
No, I didn't.
沒有?
Never?
對
No.
你不喜歡她嗎?
You're not into her, are you?
才沒有呢
No! God, not at all.
我真是氣瘋了
I am Jack's raging bile duct.
真的? 告訴我沒關係
Are you sure? You can tell me.
相信我 是真的
Believe me, I'm sure.
乾脆讓我自殺算了
Put a gun to my head and spray my brains.
那好 因為她其實兇悍的很 離她遠一點
She's a predator posing as a house pet. Stay away.
那女的說話很粗俗 我從來都沒聽過
The shit that came out of this woman's mouth, I had never heard!
天 我很久沒幹的這麼爽了
My God.I haven't been fucked like that since grade school.
泰勒當然會喜歡那種人
How could Tyler not go for that?
有一次 他把色情片剪入灰姑娘裡
The other night, he was splicing sex organs into Cinderella.
瑪拉只是需要一個撫慰的人
Marla doesn't need a lover, just a caseworker.
我們只是互相發洩
Or a wash. This isn't love, it's sport fucking.
她先是闖入我的安慰團體
She invaded my support groups
現在又闖入我家
and now my home.
嘿 坐下
Hey, hey. Sit down.
聽著 你不能跟她談我的事
Now, listen. I can't have you talking to her about me.
我幹嘛...
Why would I...
你敢跟她說我或這間房子的事
Say anything about me or what goes on in this house to her or anybody,...
我們就絕交
we're done.
- 發誓  - 好啦
- Now promise me. - OK.
發誓啊
You promise?
我發誓
Yeah, I promise.
發誓啊
Promise?
我已經發誓了啊
I just said, I promise! What...
你要發誓三次
That's three times you promised.
若我當時花幾分鐘等瑪拉死
If only I had wasted a few minutes and gone to watch Marla Singer die,
就不會這樣子了
none of this would have happened.
用力 對 用力
Harder, yes! Oh, harder, harder!
其實我可以搬到...
I could have moved to another room.
三樓 就聽不到他們的聲音
On the third floor where I might not have heard them.
可是我沒搬
But I didn't.
你在幹嘛?
What are you doing?
準備上床睡覺啊
Just going to bed.
你要接替我嗎?
Wanna finish her off?
不用 謝謝
No. No, thank you.
我找到香煙了
I've found a cigarette.
- 你跟誰說話?  - 閉嘴
- Who were you talking to? - Shut up.
我成了世界最靜的一角
I became the calm little center of the world.
我是忍者大師
I was the Zen master.
我開始寫短徘句詩
I wrote little haiku poems.
將詩用電子郵件傳給他人
I e-mailed them to everyone.
那是你的血?
Is that your blood?
有些是
Some of it, yeah.
這裡不能抽煙
You can't smoke in here.
休一天假 回家換件乾淨衣服
Take the rest of the day off. Come back Monday with some clean clothes.
重新振作一下
Get yourself together.
每個人的臉上都帶著敵意
I got right in everyone's hostile face.
對 這些是打架後的瘀青
"Yes, these are bruises from fighting."
沒錯 我很喜歡這個樣子
"Yes, I'm comfortable with that."
我受到了啟發
"I am enlightened."
放棄公寓生活和物質生活
You give up the condo life, give up all your flaming worldly possessions,
住在一個偏僻的爛房子裡
move to a dilapidated house in a toxic waste area,
回家還要面對這個
and you have to come home to this.
- 你好  - 我是縱火組的史丹警探
- Hello. - This is Detective Stern with the Arson Unit.
你公寓的事 我們有了新線索
We have some new information about the incident at your former condo.
我不確定你是否知道 有人在你門鎖上灑冷媒
I don't know if you're aware, but someone sprayed Freon into your front-door lock.
然後用鑿子打鎖引起火花的?
They used a chisel to shatter the cylinder.
我不知道
No, I wasn't aware of that.
我馬上打冷顫
I am Jack's cold sweat.
你覺得奇怪嗎?
Does this sound strange to you?
是 非常奇怪
Yes, sir, strange. Very strange.
- 炸藥...  - 炸藥
- The dynamite - Dynamite?
現場有殘留的銨酸鉀氯化鹽
left a residue of ammonium oxalate potassium perchloride.
知道那是什麼意思嗎?
Do you know what this means?
不知道
No, what does it mean?
表示那是自製的
It means it was home-made.
抱歉 我也覺得很驚訝
I'm sorry. This is just coming as quite a shock to me, sir.
就是這樣 瓦斯火苗才熄的
Whoever set this dynamite could have blown out your pilot light days before the explosion.
- 瓦斯是真正爆炸的原因  - 是誰做的?
- The gas was just a detonator. - Who would go and do that?
- 我才要問你這個呢  - 告訴他啊
- I'll ask the questions. - Tell him.
告訴他說是那些自由派份子搞得鬼
Tell him the liberator who destroyed my property realigned my perceptions.
你在聽嗎?
Excuse me. Are you there?
有啊 我只是不知道該怎麼想
I am listening. It's hard to know what to make of this.
你有什麼敵人嗎?
Have you recently made enemies who might have access to home-made dynamite?
敵人?
Enemies?
我要忘了物質生活的重要
Reject civilization, especially material possessions.
這件事很重要
Son, this is serious.
我知道
Yes, I know it's serious.
我說真的
I mean that.
我知道這件事很重要
Yes, it's very serious.
這件事對我比任何人都重要
Look, nobody takes this more seriously than me.
那間公寓等於我的生命
That condo was my life. OK?
裡面每樣傢俱都是我的最愛
I loved every stick of furniture in that place.
被毀的不只是冷冰冰的東西
That was not just a bunch of stuff that got destroyed.
被毀的是我
It was me!
我真要好好感謝大學教育
I'd like to thank the Academy.
你現在不方便討論這件事嗎?
Is this not a good time for you?
告訴他是你做的嘛
Just tell him you fucking did it!
他希望你說是你弄的
Tell him you blew it all up! That's what he wants to hear.
- 你還在聽嗎?  - 等等 你認為我是嫌犯?
- Are you still there? - Wait. Are you saying that I'm a suspect?
不是 我們只是需要再談談
No. I may need to talk to you,
若你要出遠門 記得告訴我
so you let me know if you're gonna leave town.
- 可以嗎?  - 好
- OK? - OK.
泰勒和瑪拉從不同時出現
Except for their humping, Tyler and Marla were never in the same room.
我爸媽也曾這樣好多年
My parents pulled this exact same act for years.
保險套是我們這代的玻璃鞋
The condom is the glass slipper of our generation.
遇到陌生人時就得戴上一個
You slip one on when you meet a stranger.
跳整晚舞之後 就把這東西丟掉
You... dance all night. Then you throw it away.
丟保險套 不是丟陌生人
The condom, I mean. Not the stranger.
什麼?
What?
我花一塊錢買下了這件禮服
I got this dress at a thrift store for $1.
一分錢一分貨
It was worth every penny.
這件是結婚禮服
It's a bridesmaid's dress.
這件衣服只會被珍惜一天
Someone loved it intensely for one day.
然後就被扔了
Then tossed it.
就好像聖誕樹
Like a Christmas tree.
本來很特別的
So special.
可是...
Then
轟一聲
bam!
就被丟棄路旁
It's on the side of the road.
連裝飾品都還沒拆呢
Tinsel still clinging to it.
就像被奸殺後的死人一樣
Like a sex crime victim.
內褲穿反了
Underwear inside out.
- 還被黑黑的膠帶纏起來  - 這件衣服的確很適合你
- Bound with electrical tape. - Well then, it suits you.
你喜歡我可以借你
You can borrow it sometime.
趕她走
Get rid of her.
什麼? 你來趕她啊
What? You get rid of her!
別提到我
Don't mention me.
我又回到了六歲 替父母傳話
I am six years old again, passing messages between parents.
- 你該走了吧  - 別擔心 我正要走
- I really think it's time you left. - Don't worry, I'm leaving.
我們不喜歡你來
Not that we don't love your visits.
神經病 我真的受不了你了
You are such a nutcase. I can't keep up.
我得走囉...
Gotta get off
謝謝 再見
Thanks. Bye.
你們喔...
You kids!
為什麼要浪費時間在她身上?
Why do you still waste time with her?
因為瑪拉至少想壞得徹底
I'll say this about Marla. At least she's trying to hit bottom.
我沒有嗎?
And I'm not?
插上羽毛 不等於你就是老鷹
Feathers up your butt do not make you a chicken.
今晚要幹嘛?
What are we doing tonight?
今晚...
Tonight...
要做肥皂
we make soap.
真的?
Really?
要先提煉脂肪才能做肥皂
To make soap, first we render fat.
鹽份的量要很正確
The salt balance has to be just right
所以最好的脂肪是人體脂肪
so the best fat for soap comes from humans.
等等 這是哪裡?
Wait, what is this place?
抽脂診所
A liposuction clinic.
找到了
Pay dirt!
全世界最有養分 最油的脂肪 無與倫比的
Richest, creamiest fat in the world. Fat of the land!
不要拉 不要拉
No! Don't pull it, don't pull it!
再給我一包
Give me another one.
提煉脂肪時 動物脂肪就會浮出來
As the fat renders, the tallows float to the surface.
跟童子軍時學的一樣
Like in Boy Scouts.
- 我能想像出你童子軍時的模樣  - 繼續攪拌
- It's hard to imagine you as a Boy Scout. - Keep stirring.
獸脂變硬後 除去表面的甘油
Once the tallow hardens, you skim off a layer of glycerin.
加上硝酸後 就變成硝化甘油
Add nitric acid, you've got nitroglycerin.
再加上硝酸鈉和鋸屑
Then add sodium nitrate and sawdust,
就可以做成炸藥
you've got dynamite.
做肥皂 就能做很多炸藥
Yeah, with enough soap, one could blow up just about anything.
泰勒很有小聰明
Tyler was full of useful information.
古人知道小溪哪段最能洗衣服
People found clothes got cleaner when washed at a certain point in the river.
- 知道為什麼?  - 不知道
- You know why? - No.
只要找供奉生人的那段就對了
Human sacrifices were once made on the hills above this river.
因為屍體燃燒時
Bodies burnt.
水沖刷灰燼會產生堿液
Water permeated the ashes to create lye.
這就是堿液
This is lye.
混合了屍體被燒熔的脂肪
The crucial ingredient. Once it mixed with the melted body fat,
就能排出肥皂成份進入小溪
a white soapy discharge crept into the river.
給我看看你的手好嗎?
May I see your hand, please?
你在幹嘛?
What is this?
這叫做化學灼傷
This is a chemical burn.
比其他灼傷都要痛 而且會留下疤痕
It will hurt more than any burn and it will leave a scar.
(你要幹嘛?) 這東西比癌症還要痛
Meditation worked for cancer, it could work now.
- 感受一下這種疼痛  - 噢 老天
- Don't shut the pain out. - Oh, God!
最早的肥皂都是英雄的灰燼
The first soap was made from heroes' ashes,
跟首只上太空的猴子一樣偉大
like the first monkey shot into space.
沒有痛苦和犧牲 就沒有收穫
Without pain or sacrifice, we would have nothing.
我試著不去想"灼傷"這個詞
I tried not to think of the word searing of flesh.
停下 這就是你的痛
Stop it! This is your pain, this is your burning hand.
我要到洞裡找我的精神動物
I'm going to my cave to find my power animal.
不要用快死的人的方式躲避疼痛
No! Don't deal with this the way those dead people do! Come on!
我懂你要傳達的事了
I get the point!
不 那還不夠成熟
No! You're feeling premature enlightenment.
不要錯過一生最棒的時刻
It's the greatest moment of your life, and you're off somewhere else!
我沒有
I am not!
閉嘴 我們的父親就像上帝的分身
Shut up! Our fathers were our models for God.
連父親都拋棄我們
If our fathers bailed,
更何況上帝
what does that tell you about God?
聽我說
Listen to me.
你要假設上帝不愛你
You have to consider the possibility that God does not like you.
他一直都不想要你
He never wanted you.
或許還很討厭你呢
In all probability, He hates you.
你的痛不是最悲慘的事 不是嗎?
This is not the worst thing that can happen.
我們不需要他
We don't need Him!
不需要
I agree!
去他的詛咒和贖罪
Fuck damnation, fuck redemption.
我們都是被上帝遺棄的子民
We are God's unwanted children? So be it!
我要拿水
I'm getting water!
用水澆會更糟糕的
You can use water and make it worse or...
看著我
Look at me.
用醋來中和吧
Or use vinegar to neutralize the burn.
放開我
Please let me up!
你得先放棄一切
First, you have to give up.
你必須沒有恐懼
First, you have to know, not fear,
面對你總有天會死的事實
know that some day, you're gonna die.
你不知道這有多痛
You don't know how this feels!
只有拋棄一切 才能獲得自由
It's only after we've lost everything that we're free to do anything.
好
OK.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
你越來越接近極限了
You're one step closer to hitting the bottom.
泰勒將肥皂以每條20元
Tyler sold his soap to department stores
賣給百貨公司
at $20 a bar.
不知道他們賣多少錢
God knows what they charged.
大家都說這種肥皂最好用
This is the best soap.
謝謝你 蘇珊
Thank you, Susan.
漂亮
It was beautiful.
把那些女人的脂肪賣回給她們
We were selling rich women their own fat asses back to them.
他今天打黃色領帶
He was wearing his yellow tie.
我現在根本不打領帶了
I didn't wear a tie to work any more.
"搏擊俱樂部的第一條規則就是不能提及搏擊俱樂部"
"The first rule of Fight Club is don't talk about Fight Club."
我又昏頭了
I'm half-asleep again.
一定是把那張紙忘在影印機上
I must have left it in the copy machine.
"搏擊俱樂部的第二條規則是..."這是你的?
"The second rule..." Is this yours?
假設你是我 請你替我做個決定
Pretend you're me. Make a managerial decision.
如果是你找到這個你會怎麼辦?
You find this. What would you do?
我來告訴你吧
Well, I gotta tell you,
我跟那個人說話會很小心
I'd be very, very careful who you talk to about that.
因為寫那些字的人一定很危險
Because the person who wrote that is dangerous.
這個人面怪獸恐怕會大發雷霆
And this button-down, Oxford-cloth psycho might just snap
大鬧這裡每一間辦公室
and then stalk from office to office
他會端著半自動的卡賓槍...
with an Armalite AR10 carbine gas-powered semiautomatic weapon,
逐個殺光他所有的同事
pumping round after round into colleagues and co-workers.
這個可怕的人可能是你的老友
This might be someone you've known for years.
跟你非常親近的人
Someone very, very close to you.
那些都是泰勒會說的話
Tyler's words coming out of my mouth.
以前的我是個好好先生
And I used to be such a nice guy.
不要每次撿到東西就找我
Or maybe you shouldn't bring me every piece of trash you pick up.
服務部門 你好
Compliance and Liability.
我的乳頭快爛掉了
My tit's gonna rot off.
失陪了 我得接個電話
Will you excuse me? I need to take this.
- 你說什麼?  - 替我檢查是否長乳癌了好嗎?
- What do you mean? - I need you to check for a lump in my breast.
- 去醫院啊  - 我沒錢去
- Go to a hospital. - I can't afford to waste money on a doctor.
我又不懂這個
I don't know about this, Marla.
拜託
Please.
她沒有找泰勒 因為我對她不會起邪念
She didn't call Tyler. I'm neutral in her book.
不錯嘛 拿食物給...
That's nice. Taking food to
哈尼佛 雷恩小姐 她們呢?
Mrs Haniver and Mrs Raines. Where are they, exactly?
都死了 我雖然活著 卻很窮
Tragically, they're dead. I'm alive and I'm in poverty.
要吃的嗎?
Want any?
- 不用  - 我替你留了一份
- No, no. - I got one for you.
謝謝你的好意
Thanks for the thought.
你的手怎麼了?
What happened to your hand?
沒什麼
Oh, nothing.
這裡嗎?
Right there?
- 有沒有感覺?  - 沒有
- Feel anything? - No.
再確定一下
Well, make sure.
我很確定
OK, I'm pretty sure.
你一點感覺都沒有?
You feel nothing?
沒有
No, nothing.
那就好 謝謝
Well, that's a relief. Thank you.
- 呃 這沒啥的  - 我希望我有機會報答你
- No problem. - I wish I could return the favor.
我們家族沒有人得過乳癌
Breast cancer doesn't run in my family.
- 我可以替你檢查前列腺  - 我想我那裡沒什麼問題
- I could check your prostate. - I think I'm OK.
謝謝你了
Well, thanks, anyway.
好了嗎?
Are we done?
好了 再見
Yeah, we're done. See you... around.
柯納裡斯?
Cornelius?
Cornelius!
是我啊 鮑伯
It's me! Bob!
鮑伯
Hey, Bob.
- 我們還以為你死了呢?  - 我還活著
- We all thought you were dead. - No, no. Still here.
- 你好嗎?  - 比我之前的任何時候都要好
- How are you, Bob? - Better than I've ever been in my whole life.
真的? 還參加團體課嗎?
Really? Still remaining men together?
不 我找到了更好的寄託
No, no. I got something so much better now.
真的? 是什麼?
Really, what is it?
第一條規則是
Well...
我不可以談論那件事
The first rule is, I'm not supposed to talk about it.
第二條規則是
And the second rule is
我不可以談論那件事
I'm not supposed to talk about it.
第三條規則是
And the third rule is...
鮑伯 我也是會員
Bob, Bob. I'm a member.
你看我的臉
Look at my face, Bob.
那他媽... 那他媽太好了
That's fucking... fucking great.
- 我沒見過你啊  - 我只有星期二和星期四去
- I've never seen you there. - I go Tuesdays and Thursdays.
- 我星期六去  - 恭喜你
- I go Saturday. - Congratulations.
恭喜我們兩個吧
Yeah, hey, to both of us, right?
你知道發起人是誰嗎?
Have you heard about the guy that invented it?
噢 事實上...
Yeah, actually...
我聽了好多傳說
I hear all kinds of things.
有人說他是在精神病院出生的
Supposedly, he was born in a mental institution
他一個晚上只睡一小時
and he sleeps only one hour a night.
他很偉大耶
He's a great man.
你認識泰勒德頓嗎?
Do you know about Tyler Durden?
我沒打疼你吧?
I didn't hurt you, did I?
當然有
Actually, you did.
謝謝你 謝謝
Thank you for this. Thank you, thank you, thank you.
搏擊俱樂部
Fight Club.
是我和泰勒共同的創作
This was mine and Tyler's gift.
是我們給世界的禮物
Our gift to the world.
我發現有很多新面孔
I look around, I look around, I see a lot of new faces.
閉嘴
Shut up!
表示你們沒遵守前兩條規則
Which means a lot of people have been breaking the first two rules of Fight Club.
我在這看到了最強最聰明的人
I see in Fight Club the strongest and smartest men who've ever lived.
你們都很有潛力 但都被浪費了
I see all this potential. And I see it squandered.
你們只是做一些替人加油
Goddamn it, an entire generation pumping gas.
或是上菜
Waiting tables.
或是打領帶上班的工作
Slaves with white collars.
廣告誘惑我們買車子 衣服
Advertising has us chasing cars and clothes.
於是拼命工作買不需要的東西
Working jobs we hate so we can buy shit we don't need.
我們是被歷史遺忘的一代
We're the middle children of history.
沒有目的 沒有地位
No purpose or place.
沒有世界大戰
We have no Great War.
沒有經濟大恐慌
No Great Depression.
我們的大戰只是心靈之戰
Our great war is a spiritual war.
我們的恐慌只是我們的生活
Our great depression is our lives.
我們從小看電視 相信有一天
We've all been raised on television to believe
會成為富翁 明星或搖滾巨星
that one day we'd be millionaires and movie gods and rock stars.
但是...我們不會
But we won't.
那是我們逐漸面對著的現實
We're slowly learning that fact.
所以我們非常憤怒
And we're very, very pissed off.
搏擊俱樂部第一條規則 不可以提及...
First rule of Fight Club is, do not talk...
你是誰?
Who are you?
- 我是誰?  - 對
- Who am I? - Yeah.
這家酒吧叫做盧的酒吧
There's a sign on the front that says Lou's Tavern.
我就是盧 你又是誰?
I'm fucking Lou. Who the fuck are you?
泰勒德頓
Tyler Durden.
你們怎麼可以用我的地方活動
Who told you motherfuckers that you could use my place?
我們跟艾文講好了
We have a deal worked out with Irvine.
艾文現在正在家裡療傷呢
Irvine's at home with a broken collarbone.
這又不是他的店
He don't own this place.
這是我的
I do.
- 你們給他多少錢?  - 一毛都沒有
- How much money's he getting for this? - There is no money.
真的?
Realy?
- 通通免費  - 很不可思議吧
- Free to all. - Ain't that something?
沒錯
It is, actually.
給我聽好
Look, stupid fuck!
我要你們通通滾出去
I want everybody out of here right now.
你也該加入我們的俱樂部
You should join our club.
聽到我說什麼了嗎?
Did you hear what I just said?
你跟你的朋友都可以加入
You and your friend.
這下你明白我在說什麼了嗎?
You hear me now?
我沒聽明白
No, I didn't quite catch that, Lou.
還是沒聽明白
Still not getting it.
好了 好了 好了 我知道了 我知道了
OK, OK, I got it.
操 我又忘了
I got it, I got it. Shit, I lost it.
退後 都退後
Back! All of you!
通通退後
Everybody back!
盧
Ah, Lou!
別這樣嘛 我們很喜歡這裡
Come on, man! We really like this place.
- 繼續發洩吧  - 給我閉嘴
- That's right, Lou. Get it out. - Shut the fuck up.
你覺得這樣很好笑?
Is that fucking funny?
這傢伙瘋了
Fucking guy is a loony, I'm telling you.
怎麼會這樣?
Unbelievable.
- 我受過更大的痛苦呢 盧! - 天哪 天哪
- You don't know where I've been, Lou. - Oh, my God!
我受過更大的痛苦呢
You don't know where I've been!
讓我們繼續用這裡吧 求求你
Please let us keep it, Lou! Please, Lou!
要用就用吧
Fucking use the basement! Christ!
你得向我保證 向我保證
I want your word, Lou! I want your word!
我用我媽的名譽保證
On my mother's eyes.
謝謝你了 盧
Thanks, Lou.
你也是 大個兒
You too, big guy.
下周見了
We'll see you next week.
本周 每個人都有指定作業
This week, each one of you has a homework assignment.
你們必須找一個完全不認識的人打架
You're gonna go out. You're gonna start a fight with a total stranger.
你必須引起一場打鬥
You're gonna start a fight
可是你必須打輸
and you're gonna lose.
眼光不錯喔 先生
Excellent choice, sir.
小心點 你這混蛋!
Hey! Watch out, jackass! Come on!
這份作業並不簡單
Now, this is not as easy as it sounds.
混蛋
Son of a bitch!
正常人都會儘量避免打架
Most people, normal people,do just about anything to avoid a fight.
抱歉
Excuse me!
你剛才噴到我了 你根本沒必要這麼幹
You sprayed me with your hose. That's not necessary...
傑 快打電話報警
Jay! Go call 911!
把水管放下
Put the hose down.
住手...
Stop it! Stop it!
對不起
Sorry.
我們需要談談
We need to talk.
好啊
OK.
從何談起
Where to begin?
談你經常請假的事
With your constant absenteeism?
還是你儀容不整的事?
With your unpresentable appearance?
你馬上就要接受年度考核了
You're up for review.
我一點也不驚訝
I am Jack's complete lack of surprise.
- 什麼?  - 來假設一下
- What? - Let's pretend.
假如你是交通工具部門的人
You're the Department of Transportation, OK?
當有人跟你說在撞擊測試時
Someone informs you that this company
前座支架沒有通過考驗
installs front-seat mounting brackets that failed collision tests,
車齡超過1千英里時 ?車就壞掉
brake linings that fail after 1,000 miles,
燃油噴射系統會爆炸 會燒死人
and fuel injectors that explode and burn people alive.
你會怎麼辦?
What then?
你在威脅我?
Are you threatening me?
- 不是...  - 出去 你被開除了
- No... - Get the fuck out of here. You're fired!
我有個更好的解決辦法
I have a better solution.
把我轉成外聘人員 只要付我薪水就行了
Keep me on the payroll as an outside consultant. In exchange for my salary,
我就不把這些事說出去
my job will be never to tell people these things that I know.
我不用上班 在家工作就好
I don't even have to come into the office. I can do this job from home.
你以為你是誰? 你這個瘋子
Who... Who the fuck do you think you are, you crazy little shit?
警衛?
Security!
這下我可要好好報復他了
I am Jack's smirking revenge.
你在幹嘛?
What the hell are you doing?
很痛啊!
That hurt.
你為什麼要打我?
Why would you do that?
天? 我求求你快住手
Oh, my God! No! Please stop!
你要幹嘛?
What are you doing?
天? 我求求你不要
Oh, God, no! Please! No!
我想起第一次跟泰勒打的情形
For some reason, I thought of my first fight, with Tyler.
不...
No!
到了現在 這傢伙
Under and behind and inside everything
徹底知道...
this man took for granted,
這件事真的大條了
something horrible had been growing.
你只要付我薪水就行了 我不會再出現的
Look, give me the paychecks, like I asked, and you won't ever see me again.
那是我跟他在一起最棒的一刻
Then, at our most excellent moment together...
求求你不要再打了 不要再打我了
Thank God! Please don't hit me again.
電話 電腦
Telephone, computer,
傳真機 52張週薪支票 還有48份飛機折價券
fax machine, 52 weekly paychecks and 48 airline flight coupons.
我們成了互相贊助商
We now had corporate sponsorship.
從此我們每天都能去俱樂部
This is how Tyler and I were able to have Fight Club every night of the week.
如今 在俱樂部裡 場中的人才是主角
Now, the center of Fight Club became the two men fighting.
領導人行蹤非常低調
The leader walked through the crowd, out in the darkness.
泰勒因為在湯裡尿尿 被飯店的人起訴
Tyler was now involved in a lawsuit with the Pressman Hotel over the urine content of their soup.
生命已被我自己毀了
I am Jack's wasted life.
謝謝你
Thank you, sir.
泰勒設計了新的作業
Tyler dreamed up new homework assignments.
裝在封好的信封袋裡
He handed them out in sealed envelopes.
- 聽說達勒威也有搏擊俱樂部  - 我也聽說了
- There's a Fight Club up in Delaware City. - Yeah, I heard.
賓城好像也有
There's one in Penns Grove too.
鮑伯在新塞也發現一個
Bob even found one up in New Castle.
- 那是你成立的嗎?  - 不是 我以為是你成立的
- Did you start that one? - No, I thought you did.
才不是
No.
- 停一下  - 幹嘛?
- Stop for a second. - Hey, what are we doing?
- 轉過去  - 我們要幹嘛?
- Turn around. - What are we doing?
完成任務
Homework assignment.
哪一種任務?
What kind homework assignment?
人性的犧牲
Human sacrifice.
那是槍嗎?
Is that a gun?
- 告訴我那個不是槍  - 是槍沒錯
- Please tell me it's not. - It's a gun.
- 你要幹什麼?  - 到後面等我
- What are you doing? - Meet me in the back.
- 不要跟我鬧了  - 到後面等我
- Don't fuck around! - Meet me in the back.
在這種時刻
On a long enough time line,
不管是誰都會以為死期已至
the survival rate for everyone drops to zero.
你幹嘛? 別這樣
What are you doing? Come on!
把手放到後面
Hands behind your back.
皮夾給我
Give me your wallet.
雷蒙凱艾索 貝寧街1320號A室
Raymond K Hessel. 1320 SE Banning, Apartment A.
小小的公寓房間?
Small, cramped basement apartment?
你怎麼知道?
How did you know?
爛地方的位址只有字母沒號碼
They give shitty apartments letters.
雷蒙 你要死了
Raymond! You're going to die.
我不要...
No!
這是你父母嗎? 他們得請法醫替你驗屍
Is that your mom and dad? They're gonna have to call the kindly doctor.
才能辨認出你的身份 知道為什麼嗎?
Pick up your dental records. Know why?
- 因為我要毀了你的臉  - 不要這樣...
- There'll be nothing left of your face. - Oh, come on!
過期的社區大學學生證
An expired community college student ID.
你學什麼?
What did you study, Raymond?
- 材...材料學  - 材料學?
- S... S... Stuff. - Stuff?
期中考的題目難嗎?
Were the midterms hard?
- 我問你學的什麼?  - 大多都是跟生物有關的課
- I asked you what you studied! - Biology, mostly.
- 為什麼?  - 我不知道
- Why? - I don't know.
你想要做什麼? 雷蒙凱艾索?
What did you wanna be, Raymond K Hessel?!
我的問題是 雷蒙! 你想要做什麼?
The question, Raymond, was what did you want to be?
快回答他啊 天啊 你在搞什麼啊
Answer him, Raymond, Jesus!
獸醫...
Veterinarian. Veterinarian.
動物?
Animals.
- 對 動物  - 我知道了
- Yeah. Animals and stuff. - Stuff. Yeah, I got that.
- 那表示你要念更多書  - 是要念很多很多書
- So you need more schooling. - Too much school.
- 那麼你情願死掉嗎?  - 不情願...
- Would you rather be dead? - No, please...
你情願死掉? 跪著死在便利商店的後門?
You'd rather die here, on your knees, in the back of a convenience store?
不要...求你別開槍
Please, no.
我要拿走你的駕照
I'm keeping your license.
我隨時會去看你
Gonna check in on you.
我知道你住在哪
I know where you live.
要是在六星期內你沒當獸醫
If you're not working to be a veterinarian in six weeks,
你就死定了
you will be dead.
跑回家去吧
Now run on home.
跑啊 阿甘 跑啊
Run, Forrest, run!
我有罪惡感
I feel ill.
你能想像他的感受嗎?
Imagine how he feels.
拜託 那有什麼好玩的?
Come on, this isn't funny!
那樣做有什麼意義?
What the fuck was the point of that?!
明天會是他一生中最美的一天
Tomorrow will be the most beautiful day of Raymond K Hessel's life.
他的早餐會比我們吃過的都甜美
His breakfast will taste better than any meal you and I have ever tasted.
你不得不佩服他
You had to give it to him.
- 走吧  - 他早有計劃
- Come on. - He had a plan.
泰勒的哲學越來越有道理
And it started to make sense in a Tyler-sort of way.
拋棄一切...才有自由
No fear. No distractions.
有一種能力看透並拋棄
The ability to let that which does not matter
不在乎失去一切
truly slide.
工作不能代表你
You are not your job.
銀行存款並不能代表你
You're not how much money you have in the bank.
你開的車也不能代表你
You're not the car you drive.
皮夾裡的東西不能代表你
You're not the contents of your wallet.
衣服也不能代表你
You're not your fucking khakis.
你只是平凡眾生中的其中一個
You are the all-singing, all-dancing crap of the world.
我馬上就走
I'll be out of your way in a sec.
你不需要離開啦
You don't have to go.
隨便你
Whatever.
我是說...
No, I mean...
沒關係了
It's OK.
你還參加團體課嗎?
Are you still going to groups?
是啊
Yeah.
克蘿伊死了
Chloe's dead.
克蘿伊...
Wow, Chloe.
什麼時候的事?
When did that happen?
你真的在乎嗎?
Do you care?
我不知道 很久沒想到她了
I dunno. I haven't thought about it in a while.
啊哈
Yeah, well...
或許她死了也好
It was the smart move on her part.
等等
Listen...
你這樣做有什麼好處?
What are you getting out of all this?
什麼?
What?
你為什麼一直...
I mean, all this. Why do you keep...
這樣做會讓你開心嗎?
Is this making you happy?
有時候啊
Yeah, well, sometimes.
我不懂...
I don't know. I don't understand.
為什麼虛弱的人總想往強壯的人靠攏
Why does a weaker person need to latch on to a strong person?
為什麼?
What is... What is that?
你又得到了什麼?
What do you get out of it?
這是兩回事
No... That's not the same thing at all.
我們兩人完全不同
It's totally different with us.
我們?
Us?
那是什麼意思?
What do you mean by us?
- 沒什麼 你聽到了嗎?  - 聽到什麼?
- I'm sorry. Do you hear this? - Hear what?
- 下面有聲音啊 你沒聽到嗎?  - 等等
- All that noise. Hold on. - No, wait!
你說什麼?
What did you say?
別改變話題 我得跟你好好談談
Don't change the subject! I want to talk about this.
- 你們沒有在談我吧?  - 沒有
- You're not talking about me, are you? - No.
- 什麼?  - 你那天來我家救我 算什麼?
- What? - Playing doctor. What was going on there?
- 你們在談什麼?  - 沒什麼...
- What are you talking about? - Nothing. Nothing.
我想不是吧
I don't think so.
你到底想怎樣?
What do you want?
看著我
Look at me.
不要 幹嘛?
No. What?
- 這是什麼?  - 沒什麼 不用擔心
- What is that?! - It's nothing. Don't worry.
天哪 這是誰弄的?
My God. Who did this?
一個人
A person.
男的還是女的?
Guy or girl?
你管那麼多幹嘛?
What do you care?
你幹嘛不讓我問?
What do you care if I ask?
- 不關你的事  - 你不敢說
- Leave me alone. - You're afraid to say.
- 我不怕 放開我  - 不要...告訴我
- I am not. Let me go. - No! Talk to me.
放開我 走開 不要
Let go of me!
- 我們的對話...  - 我們的對話...
- This conversation - This conversation
- 結束了  - 結束了
- is over. - is over.
我就是沒辦法討好你 對吧?
I just can't win with you, can I?
我們這樣太老套了吧
Hey, this is getting a little old!
這怎麼回事?
What is... What is all this?
你說呢?
What do you think?
為什麼要做上下鋪?
Hey, why do we need bunk beds?
你太年輕 抱歉
Too young. Sorry.
那是幹嘛?
What's all that?
若應徵人很年輕 就說他們太幼齒
If the applicant is young, tell him he's too young.
老的太老了 肥的太肥了
Old, too old. Fat, too fat.
應徵的人?
Applicant?
要他嘗試冷餓個三天三夜後
If the applicant waits three days without food or shelter,
才可以進來 開始訓練
he may enter and begin training.
訓練什麼?
Training for what?
你以為這是兒戲?
You think this is a game?
你太幼齒了 不能接受訓練
You're too young to train here, end of story.
別浪費我們的時間 快滾
Quit wasting our time. Get the fuck out of here.
給你個壞消息
Bad news, friend.
這是不可能的
It's not gonna happen.
你必須要諒解
Sorry if there was a misunderstanding.
這並非世界末日
It's not the end of the world.
走就是了
Just... go away.
走啊
Go.
你這是擅闖民宅 我們會報警
You're trespassing and I will have to call the police.
別瞪著我
Don't you look at me!
你以為你這樣就可以進來? 不可能的
You're never getting in this fucking house!
不可能 不要站在走廊上 快走開
Never. Now get the fuck off my porch! Get off my porch!
遲早...
Sooner or later,
我們都會成為泰勒所期望的人
we all became what Tyler wanted us to be.
我要進去拿鏟子出來
I'm gonna go inside and I'm gonna get a shovel.
- 拿兩件黑襯衫來  - 是的 長官
- Got two black shirts? - Yes, sir.
- 兩條黑褲子  - 是的 長官
- Two pair of black pants? - Yes, sir.
- 一雙黑靴子  - 是的 長官
- One pair black boots?  - Yes, sir.
- 兩雙黑襪子  - 是的 長官
- Two pair of Black socks? - Yes, sir.
- 一件黑外套  - 是的 長官
- One blackjacket. - Yes, sir.
- 3百塊葬儀費  - 是的 長官
- $300 personal burial money? - Yes, sir.
好吧
All right.
你太老了 肥仔
You're too old, fat man.
你的奶子太大了 別站在我走廊上
Your tits are too big. Get the fuck off my porch.
鮑伯...
Bob! Bob!
像準備升空的猴子一樣
Like a monkey ready to be shot into space.
太空猴...
Space monkey.
犧牲自己換取劃時代的成果
Ready to sacrifice himself for the greater good.
你太老了 肥仔
You are too fucking old, fatty!
還有你...
And you...
你太...
You're too fucking
頭髮太金黃了!
blond!
你們兩個都給我滾
Get out of here, the both of you!
接下去一直這樣持續著...
And so it went.
留神聽著 你們這群蛆
Listen up, maggots.
你不是什麼特別的人物
You are not special.
你不是一片美麗的獨一無二的雪花
You are not a beautiful or unique snowflake.
你跟其他生物是同樣的有機物
You are the same decaying organic matter as everything else.
泰勒組織了一支軍隊
Tyler built himself an army.
我們只是來這世界走一遭罷了
We are the all-singing, all-dancing crap of the world.
跟其他生物沒什麼兩樣
We are all part of the same compost heap.
泰勒德頓為什麼要組織軍隊?
Why was Tyler Durden building an army?
有什麼目的?
To what purpose?
用意是好還是壞?
For what greater good?
只要是泰勒 我們完全信任
In Tyler we trusted.
每次他說 工作不代表你 我就這樣...對!
When he was like, "You are not yourjob", I was like, "Yeah!"
這是怎麼回事?
Hey, what's all this?
好了
OK!
- 怎麼回事?  - 我們在慶祝
- What's going on? - We're celebrating.
- 慶祝什麼?  - 快啊
- What are we celebrating? - Go on.
我來替你拿
Let me get that for you.
百事可樂 新一代的飲料
The same great taste, Pepsi.
警方已經來到現場 等等 傑克柏署長剛剛到
Investigators are here. The Police Commissioner has arrived.
署長 能否請你說說情況?
Could you tell us what you think has happened here?
我們相信這些行動與一個...
We believe this is one of many recent acts of vandalism in the city...
地下搏擊俱樂部有關
somehow related to underground boxing clubs.
我們準備展開專項調查行動
We will be coordinating a rigorous investigation.
這就是傑克柏署長的談話
That was Police Commissioner Jacobs who just arrived on the scene
- 他剛剛來到一小時前火災的火警現場  - 她好辣啊
- of a four-alarm fire that broke out... - She's hot.
現在將現場交回攝影棚內的主播
Back to you in the studio.
- 好耶...  - 耶
- Yeah! - Yeah!
- 我的老天  - 耶
- Holy shit! - Yeah!
你們做了什麼?
What the fuck did you guys do?
大破壞計畫第一條規則是...不可以有疑問
Sir, the first rule of Project Mayhem is you do not ask questions, sir.
對付犯罪不能有拖延
The victory in the war against crime will not come overnight.
需要各位的堅持和忠誠
It will take dedication and commitment and,
最重要的 是合作
most of all, cooperation.
街頭比以前安全 市區秩序有了希望
Streets are safer now. There is hope in the inner city.
然而 這才僅僅是開始
However...This is only the begin.
我要上廁所
I gotta take a piss.
前程漫漫 所以才設計"希望"計畫
These are the first steps in a long journey. That is why we have created Project Hope.
它所涵蓋的範圍是全面性的
Project Hope will be ajoint effort
這個計畫需要大家的合作
between the police and community leaders.
不論是警方或是地方政府...這是對抗犯罪的新武器
It will be a powerful new weapon in the war against crime.
- 把他的大衣套在頭上  - 他的蛋蛋冷得發抖
- Wrap it around the top of his Hacky Sack. - His balls are ice cold.
你必須取消專項調查計畫
Hi. You're gonna call off your rigorous investigation.
開個記者會 宣佈並沒有什麼地下組織 否則...
You will publicly state there is no underground group or
他們會割掉你的卵蛋
these guys are gonna take your balls.
一顆送到紐約時報
They'll send one to the New York Times
一顆送到洛城時報
and one to the LA Times.
你要追查的人都是你所依靠的人
Look. The people you are after are the people you depend on.
他們替你煮飯 替你倒垃圾
We cook your meals. We haul your trash.
替你接電話線 替你開救護車 你睡覺時 替你守門
We connect your calls. We drive your ambulances. We guard you while you sleep.
千萬不要惹我們
Do not fuck with us.
別搞丟你的蛋蛋
Ball check!
鮑伯 走這邊
Bob, you're this way.
我們走!!
Let's go.
我感覺到事情跟以前不一樣了
I am Jack's inflamed sense of rejection.
我覺得我該射殺貓熊
I felt like putting a bullet in every panda
雖然它們極力爭取生存
that wouldn't screw to save its species.
我想用汙油將法國海灘污染
I wanted to open the dump valves on oil tankers and smother those French beaches I'd never see.
我想要呼吸混濁的空氣
I wanted to breathe smoke.
你要去哪? 神經病?
Where did you go, psycho boy?
我想摧毀美好的東西
I felt like destroying something beautiful.
帶他去醫院
Get him to a fucking hospital.
好的
Yeah.
別擔心 機場寄車 可以借用很久
Don't worry, Mr Durden. Airport parking. Long term.
你先請 德頓先生
After you, Mr Durden.
你先請
After you.
- 有什麼心事 親愛的?  - 沒事
- Something on your mind, dear? - No.
為何不告訴我大破壞計畫?
Yeah, why wasn't I told about Project Mayhem?
大破壞計畫第一條規則是 不能有疑問
First rule of Project Mayhem is you do not ask questions.
你說什麼?
What you talking about?
為什麼不一開始就讓我參與?
Why didn't you include me in the beginning?
搏擊俱樂部已經從地下室裡搬出來了
Fight Club was the beginning. Now it's left the basements
改名成大破壞計畫
and it's Project Mayhem.
搏擊俱樂部是我們倆一起創造的
We started Fight Club together. Remember?
是我們兩個人共同擁有的
It's as much mine as it is yours.
你認為這是我倆的?
Is this about you and me?
是啊 我倆一起合作的啊?
Yeah. Weren't we doing this together?
那不是我們的
This does not belong to us.
我們並不特別
We are not special.
去你的 你應該先告訴我的
Fuck that. You should have told me.
泰勒
Hey, Tyler!
去你的...泰勒!
Goddamn it, Tyler!
你要什麼?
What do you want?!
長篇大論 要我給你電子郵件?
A statement of purpose? Should I e-mail you?
- 噢...  - 要不要加入是你自己決定的!
- Oh... - You decide your level of involvement!
我會的 我要知道細節
I will! I wanna know certain things first!
大破壞行動第一條規則...
The first rule of Project Mayhem...
給我閉嘴
Shut up!
我要知道你在想什麼
I wanna know what you're thinking.
管你想什麼
Fuck what you know!
忘了你知道的一切吧 那是你的問題所在
You need forget about what you know, that's the problem.
忘了你以為的生活 友誼
Forget about what you think you know about life, friendship,
尤其是你和我的事
and especially about you and me.
那是什麼意思?
What is that supposed to mean?
你要幹嘛?
What are you doing?
你們在死前想做什麼?
What do you wish you'd done before you died?
畫個自畫像
Paint a self-portrait.
蓋個房子
Build a house.
- 你呢?  - 我不知道
- And you? - I don't know. Nothing.
- 走好自己的路  - 你必須知道
- Get in the right lane. - You have to know!
若你現在就死 你對你的生命有何感受?
If you died now, how would you feel about your life?
不知道 我覺得生命乏善可陳 我這樣說你高興了吧?
I don't know! Nothing good. Is that what you want to hear?
- 別這樣  - 說得不夠好
- Come on! - Not good enough.
別鬧了 泰勒...
Stop fucking around! Tyler!
天哪
Jesus Christ!
去你的...去你的搏擊俱樂部 去你的瑪拉
Goddamn it! Goddamn it! Fuck you! Fuck Fight Club. Fuck Marla!
我受不了你的行徑
I am sick of all your shit!
好吧
OK, man.
別再瞎搞!
Quit screwing around. Steer!
看看你
Look at you!
看看你自己 你真是可悲
Look at you. You're fucking pathetic!
為什麼? 你在說什麼?
Why? Why? What are you talking about?
你想我幹嘛要炸毀你的公寓?
Why do you think I blew up your condo?
什麼?
What?
躲到安撫團體不能解決一切
Hitting bottom isn't a weekend retreat. It's not a goddamned seminar.
別再控制一切 應拋棄一切
Stop trying to control everything and just let go!
放開
Let go!
好...
All right. Fine.
好
Fine.
我從沒出過車禍
I'd never been in a car accident.
在我替那些車禍算出數字前
This must have been what all those people felt like
那些受難者都經過這個痛苦吧
before I filed them as statistics in my reports.
可惡
Goddamn!
這是全新的生命體驗
We've just had a near-life experience!
在你的世界裡 你不自覺的
In the world I see, you're stalking elk through the Grand Canyon forests
被限制住
around the ruins of Rockefeller Center.
你的衣著為外界所定型
You'll wear leather clothes that will last you the rest of your life.
為了生存遺忘本身的才能
You'll climb the thick kudzu vines that wrap the Sears Tower.
應該往下看著密密麻麻的小生物
And when you look down, you'll see tiny figures pounding corn,
高速公路上只是空蕩蕩的
laying strips of venison in the empty car-pool lane of some abandoned superhighway.
好好照顧你自己
Feel better, champ.
然後...
And then...
泰勒?
Tyler?
泰勒走了
..Tyler was gone.
我睡著了嗎?
Was I asleep?
我有睡著嗎?
Had I slept?
突然間這房子活了起來
The house had become a living thing.
這麼多人在裡面流汗呼吸
Wet inside from so many people sweating and breathing.
這麼多人活動 房子都動了起來
So many people moving, the house moved.
像個泰勒星球
Planet Tyler.
我只能面對空牆
I had to hug the walls.
困在這幫太空猴中間
Trapped inside this clockwork of space monkeys.
你不能夠在這裡抽煙...
You shouldn't be smoking in here! You know how much ether is here!
一群人煮飯 工作 睡覺
Cooking and working and sleeping in teams.
等等...
Hang on a second.
一切都在控制當中 長官
It's under control, sir.
泰勒哪去了?
Where's Tyler?
長官 大破壞行動第一條規則
Sir, the first rule of Project Mayhem is you do not...
不可以有疑問
ask questions.
好...
Right... OK.
我變孤獨了
I'm all alone.
我父親拋下我
My father dumped me.
泰勒也拋下我
Tyler dumped me.
我徹底的心碎了
I am Jack's broken heart.
大破壞行動下一步是什麼? 只有泰勒知道
What comes next in Project Mayhem only Tyler knows.
第二條規則 是不能有疑問
The second rule is you do not ask questions.
你們給我滾開 你們給我滾開!
Get the fuck away from me! Get the fuck away!
這些人是誰?
Who are all these people?
請來的清潔公司人員
The Paper Street Soap Company.
我可以進去嗎?
Can I come in?
他不在
He's not here.
什麼?
What?
泰勒不在裡面
Tyler isn't here.
泰勒走了
Tyler went away.
他走了
Tyler's gone.
有人受槍傷了 快走開
Two gunshot wounds coming through! Make some fucking room!
怎麼回事? 怎麼回事?
What happened? What happened?
我們去處理一項任務
We were on assignment. We were supposed to kill
一石二鳥的任務
two birds with one stone.
毀掉一件藝術品
Destroy a piece of corporate art...
開始行動...
Operation Latte Thunder. Go!
順便碾碎一個連鎖咖啡店
..and trash a franchise coffee bar.
全部都按計劃執行著 長官
We had it all worked out, sir.
本來都很順利的 可是...
It went smooth until...
員警 別動...
Police! Freeze!
可是怎樣?
What?
他們開槍射中了鮑伯
They shot Bob.
射中了他的頭
They shot him in the head.
那些豬頭
Fucking pigs!
天啊
Oh, God!
- 那些混蛋  - 你們這些白癡
- Those motherfuckers! - You morons.
你們到處破壞 炸毀東西
You're running around in ski masks trying to blow things up?
還希望下場能怎樣?
What did you think was gonna happen?!
我們得快點 我們要掩滅證據
OK, quick! Get rid of the evidence.
要把屍體處理掉
We gotta get rid of this body!
- 埋了他  - 什麼?
- Bury him. - What?
帶到花園裡埋了他
Take him to the garden and bury him.
- 快點  - 動作快點
- Come on, people, let's go! - Get the fuck off!
走開...
Get away from him!
你說什麼?
What are you talking about?
他才不是什麼證據
This isn't fucking evidence.
他是個人
This is a person.
他是我的朋友
He's my friend and you're
不准你們把他埋在花園裡
not burying him in the garden!
他在大破壞行動中殉職 長官
He was killed serving Project Mayhem, sir.
他是鮑伯啊
This is Bob.
長官 在大破壞行動中
Sir, in...in Project Mayhem,
我們都沒有名字
we have no names.
你聽我說
Now, you listen to me.
他是個人 他有名字
This is a man and he has a name,
他叫做鮑伯寶森
and it's Robert Paulsen, OK?
鮑伯寶森
Robert Paulsen.
他是個人 是因我們而死的
He's a manand he's dead now because of us.
你們懂嗎?
Do you understand that?
我瞭解了
I understand.
死了之後 我們的人就有名字
In death, a member of Project Mayhem has a name.
他的名字是鮑伯寶森
His name is Robert Paulsen.
His name... is Robert Paulsen.
他的名字是鮑伯寶森
His name is Robert Paulsen.
拜託 別這樣啦
Come on, guys. Please. Stop it.
他的名字是鮑伯寶森...
His name is Robert Paulsen.
閉嘴 不是要這樣子
Shut up! This is all over with!
他的名字是鮑伯寶森
His name is Robert Paulsen.
我要去找泰勒
芝加哥
亞特蘭大
泰勒?
Tyler?
不是 我是縱火組的史頓警探
No, this is Detective Stern of the Arson Unit.
我要請你明天早上到局裡談談
I need to see you...
我去泰勒到過的每個地方
I went to all the cities on Tyler's used ticket stubs, barhopping.
我不知道怎麼回事 但只要看到某個酒吧
I didn't know how or why, but I could look at 50 different bars,
我就知道那裡有問題
and somehow I just knew.
我要找泰勒德頓 我一定要跟他談談
I'm looking for Tyler Durden. It's very important that I talk to him.
我也希望我能幫到你
I wish I could help you,
長官
sir.
不管我到什麼地方
Every city I went to,
只要我一下飛機
as soon as I set foot off the plane
就能感覺附近有搏擊俱樂部
I knew a Fight Club was close.
你看我的臉 我也是會員
Look at my face. I'm a member.
我只想知道你看到泰勒了嗎?
Now, I just need to know if you've seen Tyler.
我不能將這種訊息告訴你
I'm not exposed to bespeak any such information to you
也不能將有關的情報告訴你
nor would I, even if I had said information at this juncture,... be able.
- 你是白癡  - 我得要求你離開
- You're a moron. - I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
泰勒一直很忙碌
Tyler had been busy...
忙著在全國設立分會
setting up franchises all over the country.
我在睡覺嗎?
Was I asleep?
我睡過嗎?
Had I slept?
泰勒是我的夢魘或我是他的?
Is Tyler my bad dream, or am I Tyler's?
我只知道一個傳說
We've just heard the stories.
什麼傳說
What kind of stories?
沒有人知道他長什麼樣子
Nobody knows what he looks like.
他每三年就動一次變臉手術
He has plastic surgery every three years.
那是我聽過的最蠢的事
That's the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
邁阿密真的有搏擊俱樂部?
Is it true about Fight Club in Miami?
泰勒是不是在組織軍隊?
Is Mr Durden building an army?
我一直活在似曾相似的情境中
I was living in a state of perpetual
每到一個地方
Everywhere I went,
我都覺得自己好像也去過
I felt I'd already been there.
就像跟蹤一個隱者一樣
It was like following an invisible man.
有幹血的味道
The smell of dried blood,
到處都是骯髒的腳印
dirty, bare footprints circling each other.
還有烤雞一般的味道
That aroma of old sweat, like fried chicken.
我還能感受前一晚的打鬥感覺
The feel of a floor still warm from a fight the night before.
我每次都比泰勒晚一步
I was always just one step behind Tyler.
他的名字是鮑伯寶森...
His name is Robert Paulsen...
歡迎你回來 長官
Welcome back, sir.
你好嗎?
How have you been?
你認識我?
Do you know me?
這是測試嗎 長官?
Is this a test, sir?
不是 不是測試
No. This is not a test.
你上星期四來過了啊
You were in here last Thursday.
星期四?
Thursday?
你就站在那個地方 問我這裡的警衛狀況好不好
You were standing where you are now, asking how good security is.
情況很好 長官
It's tight as a drum, sir.
你認為我是誰?
Who do you think I am?
你真的不是在測試我?
Are you sure this isn't a test?
不是 我沒有在測試
No, this is not a test.
你是德頓先生
You're Mr Durden.
這是你給我的
You're the one who gave me this.
請系上安全帶 將座椅推到鎖定的位置
Please return your seat backs to their full upright and locked position.
- 喂?  - 瑪拉 是我
- Yeah? - Marla, it's me.
我們做過嗎?
Have we ever done it?
做什麼?
Done what?
我們做過愛嗎?
Had sex?
那是什麼蠢問題?
What kind of stupid question is that?
為什麼蠢? 就因為問我們做過還是沒做過?
Stupid because it's yes or because it's no?
- 你在惡作劇嗎?  - 不是 我必須知道...
- Is this a trick? - No. I need to know...
你不知道我們有沒有做過愛?
You wanna know if I think we were just having sex or making love?
- 我們做過了?  - 你就打電話來問這個?
- We did make love? - Is that what you're calling it?
回答我的問題 到底有沒有?
Just answer the question! Did we do it or not?!
你幹了我 又甩掉我
You fuck me, then snub me.
你愛過我 又討厭我
You love me, you hate me.
你一會兒感情豐富
You're sensitive,
一會兒又變成冷酷的混蛋
then you turn into an asshole.
這樣描述我倆的關係夠了吧? 泰勒
Does that describe our relationship, Tyler?
我的血液溫度降到了冰點
We just lost cabin pressure.
你說什麼?
What did you just say?
你怎麼回事?
What is wrong with you?
你剛才叫我什麼? 說一次我的名字
Say my name!
泰勒德頓 泰勒德頓啊 神經病
Tyler Durden! You fucking freak! What's going on?
- 怎麼回事? 我馬上過去  - 等一下 瑪拉 我不在那裡
- I'm coming over! - I'm not there!
你沒有遵守你的誓言
You broke your promise.
天啊 泰勒
Jesus, Tyler.
- 你怎麼可以跟她說我的事  - 怎麼回事?
- You fucking talked to her about me. - What the fuck is going on?
我只要求你做這一件事
I asked you for one thing.
一件非常簡單的事情
One simple thing.
為什麼其他人都以為我是你?
Why do people think that I'm you?
回答我啊
Answer me!
坐下
Sit.
回答我 為什麼其他人都以為我是你?
Answer me. Why do people think I'm you?
你知道的
I think you know.
- 我不知道  - 你知道的
- No, I don't. - Yes, you do.
為什麼其他人都以為我是你?
Why would anyone possibly confuse you with me?
我不知道
I... I don't know.
- 你想到了  - 不會吧
- You got it. - No.
千萬別惹我們
Do not fuck with us!
說啊
Say it.
因為...
Because...
說啊
Say it!
因為我們是同一個人
Because we're the same person.
沒錯
That's right.
我們都只是來這世界走一遭
We are the all-singing, all-dancing crap.
我不懂
I don't understand this.
你想改變你的生活
You wanted a way to change your life.
但是你一個人辦不到
You could not do this on your own.
你一直想要變成...
All the ways you wish you could be,
我這個的樣子
that's me.
我長得像你希望的樣子 做愛像你希望的樣子
I look like you wanna look, I fuck like you wanna fuck.
我很聰明 有能力 最重要的是
I am smart, capable and, most importantly,
我很自由 而你卻相反
I'm free in all the ways that you are not.
不...
Oh, no.
- 泰勒不在 他離開了 他走了  - 什麼?
- Tyler's not here. Tyler went away. - What?
不會吧 這太瘋狂
This isn't possible. This is crazy.
每天都有很多人這樣
People do it every day.
他們自言自語 看著自己
They talk to themselves. They see themselves as they'd like to be.
但他們沒有你的勇氣 不敢去做
They don't have the courage you have to just run with it.
為什麼不能這樣呢?
You still wrestle with it,
你有時候還是你自己
so sometimes you're still you.
我們有機會應該常常這樣
We should do this again sometime.
有時候你以為你在看著我
At times, you imagine you're watching me.
若今晚是你一次參加俱樂部
If this is your first time,
就必須打
you have to fight.
漸漸地...你讓自己變成了...
Little by little, you're just letting yourself become
泰勒德頓
Tyler Durden.
工作不代表你 財產也不代表你
You are not yourjob or how much money you have!
- 不 你有房子  - 是你租的!
- No. You have a house. - Rented in your name.
- 你有工作 你有生活  - 你晚上兼差 因為你睡不著
- You have jobs, a life. - You work nights because you can't sleep.
所以你作肥皂
Or you stay up and make soap.
- 你為什麼要跟瑪拉上床?
- You're fucking Marla, Tyler.
技術上來說 跟她上床的人是你
Technically, you are.
對她來說都是你
It's all the same to her.
天哪
Oh, my God.
你發現難題了吧?
Now you see our dilemma.
她知道的太多了
She knows too much.
我們得考慮一個解決的方法
I think we're gonna have to talk about how this might compromise our goals.
你說什麼?
What... What are you saying?
簡直是胡扯... 我不聽
This is bullshit. This is bullshit, I'm not listening to this!
- 你發瘋了  - 沒有 瘋的是你
- You are insane! - No. You're insane.
我們沒有時間說這些了
We simply do not have time for this crap.
這裡就是所謂的劇情急轉直下
It's called a changeover.
電影繼續下去
The movie goes on
但是觀眾還是一頭霧水
and nobody in the audience has any idea.
先生 你要退房了嗎?
Sir! Are you checking out?
是的
Yeah. Bill me.
請先付這兩通電話費
Can you initial this list of phone calls?
- 這通是什麼時候打的?  - 是淩晨2點到3點半間打的
- When were these made? - Between 2.00 and 3.30 this morning.
我是否每天都提早睡覺?
Have I been going to bed earlier every night?
我後來有睡覺嗎? 我變成泰勒的時間越來越長了?
Have I been sleeping later? Have I been Tyler longer and longer?
有人在嗎?
Is anybody here?
似曾相識 又開始了
All over again.
有足夠的肥皂 就可炸毀一切
With enough soap, one could blow up anything.
天?
Oh, my God.
1888號
1888.
請問這是哪裡?
Who am I calling?
法蘭克林街1888號?
1888 Franklin. This is maintenance.
喂?
Hello?
法蘭克林街1888號?
1888 Franklin Street?
對 有事嗎?
Yes. Can I help you?
- 喂?  - 是
- Hello? - Yeah, yeah.
有 我要跟你們老闆說話
I need to talk to your supervisor right away.
我就是
Speaking.
聽我說
OK, listen to me.
你們大樓馬上有緊急事件發生
Something terrible is about to happen to your building.
一切都在控制之中 長官
It's under control, sir.
你說什麼?
Excuse me?
別擔心我們 長官
Don't worry about us, sir.
我們沒問題的
We're solid.
2160號
2160.
瑪拉...瑪拉...等等
Marla! Marla! Hey, wait!
等等 我必須跟你談談 瑪拉...
Wait! I gotta talk to you! Marla! Marla!
你們這些光頭佬 總是找我麻煩 打我的手臂!
Your bald freaks hit me with a fucking broom! They almost broke my arm!
整天燒手指頭 臭死了
They were burning their fingertips with lye.
聽我說 我現在只相信你 你一定要聽我說
This needs a tremendous act of faith on your part, but hear me out.
- 又來你那套花言巧語了  - 你要信任我
- Here comes an avalanche of bullshit. - A little more faith than that.
你說什麼我都不想聽
I don't wanna hear anything you have to say.
你有權利...
You have every right to be...
我只要一杯咖啡就好
I'll just have a coffee, thanks.
長官 你點什麼都是免費的
Sir. Anything you order is free of charge, sir.
為什麼免費?
Why is it free of charge?
- 不要發問  - 管他的
- Don't ask. - Whatever.
我要烤雞 湯 什麼都要
I'll have the clam chowder, fried chicken and baked potato and a chocolate chiffon pie.
要乾淨的食物
Clean food, please.
我建議不要是蛤蜊湯
In that case, may I advise against the clam chowder.
不要蛤蜊湯
No clam chowder. Thank you.
我給你30秒
You got about 30 seconds.
我知道我的行為很怪
I know I've been acting very strange, OK?
感覺好像是兩面人
I know it seems there's two sides to me...
兩面? 你根本是百面人
Two sides? You're Dr Jekyll and Mr Jackass.
你要罵我什麼都可以
I know.
我終於搞清楚了一件事
But I realized something important.
什麼事?
What?
我到現在才瞭解
The nature of our relationship wasn't clear
我倆的關係 重要的是
to me for reasons I won't go into.
- 我對你一直很不好  - 是啊...
- I know I haven't treated you well. - Whatever.
不...15秒 15秒
No, no. Fifteen seconds, please!
不要講話 完了就走
Fifteen seconds, don't open your mouth.
我想說我很抱歉
I'm trying to tell you I'm sorry.
我終於瞭解 我真的喜歡你 瑪拉
What I've come to realize is that I really like you, Marla.
真的?
You do?
真的 我很喜歡你
I really do.
我不希望因為我而帶給你厄運
I care about you and I don't want anything bad to happen to you because of me.
瑪拉 你有生命危險
Marla, your life is in danger.
什麼?
What?
你必須離開這裡
You need to leave town for a while.
- 別留在大城市裡 去露營都行  - 你發神經病了
- Get out of any major city. Just go camping... - You're an insane person.
沒有 我發現很可怕的事...
No. I've involved you in something terrible.
不...閉嘴!
No. Shut up!
- 你不安全  - 閉嘴...
- You're not safe. - Shut up!
我努力過了 我真的努力過了
Listen, I tried, Tyler. I really tried.
我知道
I know you did.
你有些特點我很欣賞
There are things about you I like.
你很聰明 幽默
You're smart, funny.
尤其床上功夫一流
You're spectacular in bed.
可是...
But
你實在很難相處
you're intolerable.
你有很嚴重的情緒問題
You have very serious emotional problems.
你應該去看心理...
Deep-seated problems for which you should seek professional help.
我知道 對不起
I know, and I'm sorry.
好 你對不起 我對不起 大家都對不起
You're sorry, I'm sorry. Everyone's sorry.
我無法再這樣繼續下去了
I can't do this any more.
真的
I can't.
我也不想
And I won't.
我要走了
I'm gone.
你不可以這樣... 瑪拉 你不安全
You can't leave, Marla! You're not safe!
- 瑪拉 你不瞭解  - 不要碰我 走開
- Marla, you don't understand! - Leave me alone!
- 瑪拉 我只是想要保護你  - 放開我
- Marla, I am trying to protect you! - Let go!
我不想再見到你了
I don't ever wanna see you again!
沒關係 如果那是代價
That's fine...
在這裡等
Here, wait right here!
等一下
Hold it right there!
安靜 安靜
Shut up! Shut up!
帶這些錢上車去
Take this money and get on this bus.
我保證以後絕對不騷擾你
I promise I won't bother you again.
安靜
Shut up!
請你上車 請你上車
Please get on the bus. Please get on the bus.
你為什麼要這樣做?
Why are you doing this?
因為你的生命有危險
They think you're a threat.
我現在沒辦法解釋
I can't explain it now,
相信我就是了
just trust me!
別讓我看見你要去哪裡 否則你就會有生命危險
If I know where you are, you won't be safe.
我可不還你錢喔
I'll keep this,
我把這當作你應該給我的
it's asshole tax.
拿去吧 這幾天千萬不要到大城市去
Fine. Remember, stay out of major cities.
泰勒
Tyler.
你是我一生中遇過最可怕的人
You're the worst thing that ever happened to me.
你好
Hello.
我要自首
I need you to arrest me.
我是犯下好幾宗縱火 暴力
I am the leader of a terrorist organization responsible
及破壞行動的地下組織領導人
for numerous acts of vandalism and assault all over this city.
都會區或許有好幾百個人員
In the metropolitan area, we had probably 200 members.
目前至少有五個城市裝好炸彈 準備引爆
Chapters have sprung up in five or six other major cities already.
這是很有組織的行動
This is a tightly-regimented organization
不用領導人物 也能做得到
with many cells capable of operating independent of central leadership.
你們到佩波街1537號那裡查查
Go to the house, OK? 1537 Paper Street.
那是我們的總部
That's our headquarters.
在房子後面的花園地下
In the back, buried in the garden,
埋有鮑伯寶森的屍體
you'll find the body of Robert Paulsen.
到地下室去 裡面有個浴缸
In the basement, you're gonna find some bathtubs
那是專門做鹽酸的地方
that have been used very recently to make large quantities of nitroglycerin.
我相信他們最新的計畫
I believe the plan is to blow up
是炸掉各家信用卡的總部
the headquarters of these credit card companies
還有經濟大樓
and the TRW building.
為什麼選擇這些大樓?
Why these buildings?
為什麼要炸毀信用卡公司?
Why credit card companies?
如果一切的記錄都被銷毀 我們全都會回到原來的起點
If you erase the debt record, then we all go back to zero.
你們最好查一下
You'll create total chaos.
看好他 我去打個電話
Keep him talking. I need to make a phone call.
我很佩服你的勇氣
I really admire what you're doing.
什麼?
What?
這樣做需要很大的勇氣
You're a brave man to order this.
你是個天才 長官
You're a genius, sir.
你說不管誰洩露大破壞行動 即使是你
You said if anyone ever interferes with Project Mayhem, even you,
也必須受罰
we gotta get his balls.
反抗也沒用 你真的很堅強
Don't fight. It's a powerful gesture, Mr Durden.
- 為我們樹立了一個榜樣  - 你們犯了一個很大的錯
- It will set an example. - You're making a big mistake!
- 你說過你會說這句話  - 我不是泰勒德頓
- You said you'd say that. - I'm not Tyler Durden!
你也說過你會說這句話
You told us you'd say that too.
我是泰勒德頓沒錯
All right. I am Tyler Durden.
聽我說 我要下直接命令
Listen to me. I'm giving you a direct order.
我們要馬上放棄行動
We're aborting this mission now.
你說你一定會說這句話
You said you would definitely say that.
等一下
Hold on.
你們瘋了 你們是員警啊!
Are you fucking out of your minds? You're police officers!
要不要來點這個...
Is somebody timing this?
給我閉嘴 可惡
Keep your mouth shut. Shit!
我們得到一些已經證實的消息
Some of this information checks out.
- 準備到那裡去看看吧  - 好的
- Let's go to that house on Paper Street. - Be right there.
嘿 等等
Hey, wait!
- 我抓到了  - 長官 我們必須帶你去
- I got him. - Sir, we have to do this.
- 停下  - 橡皮筋呢?
- Stop fighting! - Where's the rubber band?
不要碰我 把刀放下 放下
Get away from me! Drop that fucking knife!
退後
Back up.
馬上給我趴下
Face down on the floor right now!
快趴下
Get down on the floor!
誰先出來 就先吃子彈
The first person that comes out of this door gets a lead salad! Understand?
走開
Get away! Stay away!
我一直跑
I ran.
跑到全身快爆炸 快不能呼吸
I ran until my muscles burned and my veins pumped battery acid.
然後繼續跑
Then I ran some more.
你在幹嘛
What the fuck are you doing?
穿著內褲到處跑 夥計 你看起來象個神經病
Running around in your underpants! You look crazy!
我知道你的計畫
No. I'm onto you. I know what's going on here.
別這樣嘛 我還要看好戲呢
Come on, then. I got us a great place to watch from.
我們一起來吧
It'll be like pay-per-view.
- 天?  - 你現在要幹嘛?
- Oh, Christ. - Now what are you doing?
- 我要阻止這件事  - 為什麼?
- I'm stopping this. - Why?
- 這是我們做過最偉大的事  - 不...我不能讓這種事發生
- The greatest thing you've ever done. - I can't let this happen.
其他10棟大樓裡還有炸彈呢
There are 10 other bombs in 10 other buildings.
去你的 我們從什麼時候開始殺人了?
Since when is Project Mayhem about murder?
那些大樓都是空的
The buildings are empty.
大樓裡的警衛都是我們的人 我們不是在殺人 我們是在釋放那些人
We're not killing anyone. We're setting 'em free!
鮑伯死了 他們一槍轟了他的頭
Bob is dead. They shot him in the head.
我要犧牲小我完成大我
You wanna make an omelette, you gotta break some eggs.
我不理你了 你根本不存在
No. I'm not listening to you. You're not even there.
要是我就不會這麼做
I wouldn't do that. Not unless you knew which wires were what.
如果你知道 我就會知道
If you know, I know.
或許我知道你知道什麼 所以我花了整天的時間...
Or maybe I knew you'd know, so I spent all day
想著錯誤的那條線
thinking about the wrong ones.
你覺得怎樣?
You think?
不是綠色的
Oh, heavens, no. Not the green one.
最好不要割斷綠色那條
Pull any one but the green one.
請你不要這樣做
I asked you not to do that!
可惡! 離那裡遠一點
Fuck! Tyler, get away from the van.
離那裡遠一點
Tyler, I'm not kidding! Get away from the van!
可惡
Goddamn it!
好 你對你的好朋友開槍
OK. You are now firing a gun at your imaginary friend
在400加侖的炸藥的旁邊
near 400 gallons of nitroglycerin!
泰勒...
Cool it, Tyler!
別這樣嘛 不要走
Come on! Don't go!
什麼?
What?!
還有三分鐘
Three minutes.
精彩時刻就要到了
This is it.
一切重新回到原來的起點
The beginning. Ground zero.
這大概就是我們的故事開始的地方吧
I think this is about where we came in.
你想說幾句話紀念這個偉大的時刻嗎?
Do you have a speech for the occasion?
你說什麼?
I'm sorry?
我還是沒想到要說什麼
I still can't think of anything.
重演幽默片段
Flashback humor.
越來越刺激了
It's getting exciting now.
還有兩分鐘半
Two and a half.
想想我們過去的成就吧
Think of everything we've accomplished.
我們將從這面窗戶外 看到經濟事件的歷史鏡頭
Out these windows, we will view the collapse of financial history.
離經濟自由時刻又近了一步
One step closer to economic equilibrium.
她怎麼會在這裡?
Why is she here?
她逃不掉的
Tying up loose ends.
放我下來
Put me down, you baldheaded fuck!
我求求你 不要這樣做
I beg you, please don't do this.
不是我做的
I'm not doing this.
是我們倆一起做的
We are doing this.
- 我們兩個都想這樣  - 不是
- This is what we want. - No.
我不想要這樣
I don't want this.
沒錯 可是現在你的已經沒有意義了
Right. Except you is meaningless now.
我們得把你忘了
We have to forget about you.
你是我腦中的聲音而已
You're a voice in my head.
你也只是我腦中的聲音
You're a voice in mine!
- 為什麼我無法幹掉你?  - 你需要我
- Why can't I get rid of you? - You need me.
不 我真的 再也不需要你了
No. I don't. I really don't any more.
我是你創造出來的
You created me.
我可不會為了讓自己好過點 就創造你這樣的東西出來
I didn't create some loser alter ego to make me feel better.
負點責任吧
Take some responsibility.
我有
I do.
我願意為這一切負責 我接受這一切
I am responsible for all of it and I accept that.
我求求你了 請你取消這一切吧
So, please, I'm begging you, please call this off.
我曾經讓我們失望過嗎?
Have I ever let us down?
因為我 你成長了不少吧?
How far have you come because of me?!
我會照顧著你的
I will bring us through this.
跟以前一樣 我會保護你 即使你又哭又鬧
As always, I will carry you kicking and screaming
最後你還是會感謝我的
and in the end you will thank me.
我很感謝你
Tyler. Tyler.
謝謝你為我做的一切
I'm grateful to you. For everything that you've done for me.
可是這次太誇張了 我不想要這個
But this is too much. I don't want this.
那你要什麼?
What do you want?
回去做原來的爛工作?
Your shitjob back?
爛公寓 看爛電視劇 去他的! 我才不要這樣幹
Fucking condo world, watching sitcoms? Fuck you! I won't do it.
- 天啊 這事可不能夠發生  - 已經都準備好了 閉嘴
- This can't be happening. - It's already done, so shut up!
60秒 乖點
60 seconds till CRI.
我可以解決的 這些都是假的
I can figure this out. This isn't even real.
你不是真實的 那槍...槍也不是真在你手上
You're not real, that gun... That gun isn't even in your hand.
槍在我手上
The gun's in my hand.
你那樣做也沒有用的
Good for you. It doesn't change a thing.
你幹嘛拿槍頂著自己的腦袋
Why do you wanna put a gun to your head?
不是我的頭 泰勒
Not my head, Tyler.
是我們兩個的頭
Our head.
很有趣
Interesting.
你想要怎麼樣?
Where are you going with this, Ikea boy?
這可是我們倆的事
Hey. It's you and me.
朋友?
Friends?
泰勒
Tyler,
我要你認真的聽我說
I want you to really listen to me.
好的
OK.
我的眼睛睜開著
My eyes are open.
什麼味道?
What's that smell?
- 其他人呢?  - 我不知道 怎麼回事?
- Where is everybody? - Oh, no. What's going on?
德頓先生
Mr Durden!
天啊
Oh, my God!
你...你沒事吧 長官?
Are you... Are you all right, sir?
哦 是的 我沒事
Oh, yeah, I'm OK.
你看起來很糟糕 長官 怎麼回事?
You look terrible, sir. What happened?
哦 沒什麼 沒事的
Nothing, it's no problem.
哦 不 長官...
No, no, no, sir.
他說的很對 你看起來很不好 你需要馬上治療
He's not kidding. You look awful. You need assistance.
我很好
I'm fine.
你看 我很好 一切都很好
Look, I'm fine... Everything's fine.
這是幹什麼?
Stop it!
放開她
Let her go.
你...
You!
嗨 瑪拉
Hi, Marla.
把她留在這裡 你們把東西收拾一下 到樓下會合
Leave her with me. Meet me downstairs.
你確定?
Are you sure?
是的 我很確定
Yes, I'm sure.
你這個混蛋 你在玩什麼無聊的遊戲
You fucker! What kind of sick fucking game are you playing at?!
居然帶我來...天? 你的臉...
Putting me on a...Oh, my God, your face!
我知道
Yeah, I know.
怎麼回事?
What happened?
不要問
Don't ask.
你被槍打傷了
You're shot.
沒錯
Yes, I'm shot.
天啊
Oh, my God.
- 不敢相信他還能站著  - 真強悍!
- I can't believe he's standing. - One tough motherfucker.
誰開的槍?
Who did this?
我自己開的 找點棉紗來
I did, actually. Find some gauze.
你開槍射你自己?
You shot yourself?
對 沒事的
Yes, but it's OK.
瑪拉 看著我 我真的沒事
Marla, look at me. I'm really OK.
相信我 一切都沒事了
Trust me. Everything's gonna be fine.
我們相遇的時候 碰巧是我人生中最詭異的一段時間
You met me at a very strange time in my life.